Don't you see rubies dripping from my hair like rice?
Size!
They name her, you chished of a half-eating grace
Chandelini barefoot on the threshold of place
Where jasmine borders wilt into wilderness
And purity unlearns its own loneliness
Not in the lotus-white halls where mantras are in
I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't know what I'm talking about, I don't
Breakfast like disaster is a farm Someone hit the relics in the laundry by the
stairs Someone's acting casual
Like the sweet forbidden hymns like he dreams, but we don't
Sorry, so
It's okay
Oh my god
So they kind of think about the cool happens today when I woke up. Well, you know, it would be cool if tricks was back, right?
but
They woke up and I walked by there's like, you know, I thought it was like a little nor laying there and then
And then I walked down, I saw like Cole Norris on the other side of the room and I looked back and it was like, it was her brother, it was her brother.
He was like, can you guys hear me yet? Or my microphone?
And it was her, I have this black cat, like when he was from the litter too, but he's been gone for over like a year.
Um and it's like but he would always you know tricks would always chase him out
But he was sleeping right there, and I have like pictures of it was so cute
I have a couple I did I should have taken better pictures, but I just was like keeping my distance a little bit
I did go over and pet him eventually, but
And he got he kind of like was like you know a little bit
But then he just then he like I think he left again or unless he's like in another room
I don't like really looked and some also somebody so maybe put in it
They were so nice enough to put in it add on Craigslist
For me what if it's a picture here? Oh
Shit, I need to make it big. Well, I'm sorry like all small
Hi guys, he didn't come back. Yeah, it's like
That's somebody put it out in Craigslist. Oops. I
Don't want I don't want to show the name
Oh, my green screen is like too crazy. Sorry guys
Okay, oh my god
Oh, hold on hold on one second. Oh
It's my fault one second
Um
Yeah, oh, yeah, so, um, anyway the cats are eating like chicken nuggets right now
But yeah, but the cat was there and he's he was sitting there. Did you see the picture?
Oh, I mean, it's like I should really I wish I could show the picture bigger music. I didn't show up very very good
But this is like a full screen. Yeah, I can do this
I was like sitting there
His name is his name is Tux. He's like a tiny little bit of a
White on his chest. I mean, I wish I mean I had since he was a kid and like he was born here and stuff, right?
But then like and then he was like he's just like inside
It's once they seem big but though it's like it's like it's like only ever
I've been all the same here. I look like he was gone like and it's like I don't but he not he didn't get like
Growl that by the other cats like like because tricks would always growl at any other cat that came in the house besides just
Except for Rudy. He was always good with Rudy, right? But um, but if his brothers ever came back he would get
And but somebody this guy this guy named Ben. I'll just say the name is Ben
Then the two of us
Oh, the link. Okay. Hold on. Yeah, Benjamin. All right. I love those guys. Like his name is Ben and he like he put it out for me
I was like, oh no, there's another guy named Ben that puts ads on Craigslist, but he's not so nice
But this guy posted a really nice ad on Craigslist and I was like, I think I have an ad on next door
I just I just renewed it and stuff
You know, I've had some pet psychic kind of like people like with leads and stuff, but
At the end of the day, like I just like I think that it's like not a bad area for cats to like wander often
Because there's probably like good places for the cats to go. I'll invite to go so on
So yeah, I'm and I want to thank you. Okay, there we go
But um, let me see so what what's every 19 people
I love it. I love it. I love it and fried it like it's like a stable one and stuff.
They're so hot. It's like when you come up, of course, once you come up and say hello,
I wonder if he's going to be nice tonight.
Hello.
Hey.
Are you doing what is that the train whistle? Yeah
Why do you look so close to a train? It was that was that like a deterrent to move is it gobbled in the middle of the night?
Well, I have to talk. I found you a boyfriend, brother
You did who?
He's very nice. He's actually live right now. He's a very nice guy. He doesn't like
By you
Well, he's a very nice guy and he hosts open panels, but he doesn't want to be the hobo
Very rich guy very rich
He's a rich hobo with what's going on?
How can you be rich?
How loud is that train like right next to the train and the tracks what's going on?
It's so loud
I think you say why it was so long.
It's so loud because you're next to me.
You've gone deaf from the train whistle.
I mean, come on.
Listen, if you don't want it, I found you a boyfriend.
If you don't want it, that's fine.
Are you a hobo ghost?
I think that it says you're a hobo.
No.
Are you a boho?
What does that mean?
I don't know.
Do you know what the fuck you're talking about right now?
No, I smoke too much weed, I think.
Doesn't make much of it. I'm just eating it like
You should have come up on the panel. I found you a man. I
Fucking found you
Running around for some man. I don't ever seen if you found me a woman. I wouldn't be disrespectful
Why does everyone want me to find them a woman and then they're like, oh, yeah, and then I'll have
Do you want to have sex close it was that you're saying no, I'm good. Just forget about it. What if there's another woman there?
What if there's I try to talk to you sometimes, but you know, what if what if Q is there?
He's really cute and he's a twink
Into that
He's a hobo, no, I'm sorry. He's not my hobo. He doesn't a nice
What
What do you mean? What?
Well, you got quiet else.
You make it awkward as fuck and you say what to me?
I made it awkward.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean I thought we could joke around like guys.
Yeah, we were joking around.
I found you a man.
Yo, but yeah, who's this man?
Why don't you have him come over here?
I don't feel like going to some stranger's show.
I'm a celebrity on YouTube.
I don't just go.
It's not my fucking show.
I don't know these guys.
Why are you saying he's a bad boy?
He's he's he's he's he's he's
he's he's he's he's he's he's
Don't have a threesome, you know
You know I'm trying to be friendly because you know I love you sometimes it's hard to talk to you, man
I'm like I'm so easy. I heard are you easy always easy to talk to
What channel depends what channel?
You know my channel about my channel right now pretty easy
Other channels I like to debate
Like literally there's like four train tracks and like again, dude, who's the train coming by?
Sorry. Oh
My god, are you serious? It's so loud. You're gonna you're gonna disrespect me after I found you
He I thought you wait. Hey, don't do that
You look pretty good brother not doing anything. Yes. Yes. I come in your background. You're being this is stuck on right now
Well every time I talk
Now go ahead and coast oh
Now you're gonna do flight. No, you're not like you have the flight first. I fucking knew you were gonna do that
You know what
I'm no longer gonna tell you a boyfriend now. I'm not gonna fucking now you now. I'm gonna say he shouldn't join
Are you actually
You don't sound very sorry
Here is the official ghost sound
You get it boo because you're a ghost
I'm sorry.
You think it's cool to be disrespectful?
What was a joke?
You can say sorry, are you?
I mean, how do you say sorry, bro?
Are you mad at me?
A little bit.
Like a tiny bit.
We're not dating, because then I repair,
I might.
No, what you say you see you've got you've got it you you get you're all confused
Falls you sent me a picture of your toes. You're just gonna yell. He's gonna crash over your toes the ladders randomly out of nowhere
That's all I'll say that was a joke that was a joke. Okay
But you did you did, right? And then we're just
Assumed that I did what would you be argument against that you gave me?
I mean is that I think I'm not gonna another man your pictures of your feet your toes
You're not no, I don't think it's Gary are charging me money. You didn't charge me money to send you my
Why do you want one with me for I'm
No, no, no, no one would want to buy that picture.
I'm burning those pictures.
It's like, I don't want to be rude to you, you know.
I don't want to be rude and say it.
Oh, then you had a chance with that woman.
Okay.
You had a chance to be what you did.
Then you ask her if she was a woman.
You have to ask her again and again and she got offended eventually.
You had a chance to be smart in the womb, but guess what? God didn't have your back on that one.
In the womb?
Yup, in the womb. Here we got it.
Oh, well.
For fuck's sake, God. I gotta take care of you.
You're like my little brother. I gotta take care of you and shit.
Hey, so what?
Make it hard make it harder brother. Yeah, you do you know you do don't put it down
These fries are so good. Oh
I'm gonna do some
Don't
Don't are you talking about Jesus?
Religious whatever you want to talk about. Oh my god. It's really embarrassing. Is that really embarrassing picture?
Oh that you bake lips. You might see in the thumbnail. I don't know if it's a big
Can you wipe your mouth off?
Yes, you have a ma you have a nappy. I do. I don't have a nap. You want to take a nap?
Sure
That's good. Well, you're taking it happy. You just started your payment. I don't feel like you I'm gonna be drinking coffee right now
I'll be staying away. I offered you to come over to the you offer me. You do it. I did all
What do you get fine is offer I'm like a big brother. I'm gonna get pissed off dude
You pissed me off like you asked me right when I started doing it. Would I over just another person's show that I don't
Say no, that's all you have to say
did I said no thank you I said okay then fuck it leave it alone but you're
pissing me off dude but I'm just telling you the truth no you keep
fucking you keep pushing and pushing and pushing and expect me not to go like
you keep pushing and pushing and are you gonna crash out on me no I'm not gonna
crash out but Jesus Christ yeah I'm maybe at this point yeah I might I might
crash on you I might do it
No pushing I was supposed to react to like you know, I'm just gonna kick me you're gonna kick me now
Oh, that's all you do
That's all you do you run away from the
Green right now, I'm not even on the screen that I can't even see you
But I can see yeah, am I close you're pushing it. All right, I'm over
I'm gonna argue. I forgot what I was looking at. It's like arguments your little brother. It's like
I'm not even on the screen.
Oh, I'm got another fucking
part of your Jesus Christ.
Look, we have a guest.
We have a guest every night.
Who?
Who are you imitating?
Is that me?
I don't want to, I don't want to,
I don't want anyone imitating me.
Excuse me. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I'm describing this in the fucking pain. You thought it was gonna come out normal motherfuckers
Why I didn't think you come out like this that place is fucked up and it's a fucked up place
Not normal anymore. I'm fucked up
This is how it's gonna be. This is how it's gonna fucking be from now on, man.
You did thumbnail of my, you see my thumbnail that Bakelips made that I used?
No, no, no. I didn't see shit, man. I just came up with it.
You get Bakelips? Oh my gosh. I forgot.
I mean, I, I, I have to ask him if he tells me to take it off.
Pool Gate Clips? What do you do now?
Now, I think I should be able to use a picture of me,
like, like, he's like this, like,
but it's not even a picture of me,
because that'd be kind of crazy if I was like,
like that, but I think maybe there's been nights
that I have, maybe have a little bit closer to that,
but those, not my best nights and stuff,
but, you know, I think I'm just,
what are you saying?
What are you saying, man?
I'm just saying, did you see the thumbnail of this,
of this show?
No, I didn't look.
I didn't look at it.
It's horrific.
It's like big clips through it.
You can't show it.
You don't have the power to show it.
I can.
I can show it.
Hold on.
I'm going to show it, man.
You got skills.
I don't have a hand.
Did you just hit ghost or did he leave?
He left.
He said, I know.
Good.
Good, good, good, good.
Because I really don't want to hear his bullshit right now.
Did you see this one?
Oh, who made that?
That's great.
Who made that?
It looks just like you.
Oh, please.
You got this face like, oh, give me money.
Give me money.
Oh, shut up.
Ha, ha, ha.
Can you do a reading it's been a while I can't but I'm eating McDonald's right now. So it's okay. Okay. Okay. I'll wait
I'm sure you haven't eaten all day go ahead and do something real quick
Yeah, I'm trying to I've been feeling sick lately. I wanted to get a positive reading from you. Maybe I'll get I think you're reading without even
I just need one card. Honestly, that's that's okay. I'll give you a card
Okay, as long as it's not that Alice in Wonderland bullshit. I don't
See you don't have a like
Jamie's cowboys Jamie's cowboys. How is Jamie's cowboys? She's a loyal follower of psyches channel
Bakelips he got skills
Look how he made the the psychedelic shit behind you. He made it like you're fucking crazy like you're high on some shit
Well, this is like the five of course, which is like a five of the five of cups
Yeah, which is like pretty much like you know kind of like you have some kind of regret in the past
I do do going to Dougie's channel was the biggest regret I ever had is that Lenore? Oh my gosh. Yeah
Okay, it's Lenore. I'm like stripping because the other black cat came back today, you know
Um, and he was like there at like laying in the bed
Well, this is like some kind of sadness in the past, but it's like, you know
Time heals all wounds kind of thing and like, you know, sometimes crying is good, too
It's like healthy for you know, just to like get out even so last time you cried
around I think about Danny I think I was like I like said a few tears around the
time that we were watching like whenever I put things with music and stuff and
then I think but then I bet I don't cry like that like usually I would only
cry with somebody I basically you know I cry every day thinking about Michael
the greenie oh every day that wasn't even Michael the greenie whatever his name
was I cry every day about that poor guy
You do you really like him that much? Yeah, I didn't like him, but I do cry about it. Yeah, I like him
You didn't even like him. I said no. He's a fucking asshole
well, I
I should play so I have old clips of them as I do you see you
We've been on the show for a long time too
It's like I have quite a show like and now I have this cult codex and it's like
You're right right right now. It's like
Everything's free on it except for, like, the, um, the, uh...
Excuse me, excuse me.
No problem. Everything's free except for, like, the...
I put the transcripts behind a kind of paywall
and everything, because it made them searchable and everything,
because there's, like, half a million trans...
Like, like, in the archives, and there's, like, so much.
There's, like, thousands of hours of shows.
So, like, if I don't make it,
I want you to put up a memorial to me for a year, okay?
Just leave a band with my face on for a year.
Should I just pray Gaudi on it?
Immemorium, immemorium to God.
What, God is dead?
Should I do like Nietzsche, God is dead?
No, no, no, no, don't go that deep with it.
Just say, Immorium to God.
You sound very existential.
My favorite guest.
That's why I want you to write, my favorite guest.
You want me to lie?
Yeah.
No.
All right, I don't mind about things.
Thank you for that reading, by the way.
So I-
Oh my God.
It just means that you can get over any kind of sadness,
I believe.
It's like, you know, it's like, we all,
and we all have like things that we can be very sad about,
but it's like the good thing is the heart does heal.
And it's like, just like, like I'm so sad about the tricks,
but my other cat just like, just showed right back up
and haven't seen him for over a year.
And he's beautiful too.
And it's like, maybe it's just like,
they know when they want to be-
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
The cat that you lost is gone and never came back.
A new cat came back?
Yeah, and like the one I've had, like he, the one, his brother, yeah.
You're kidding me.
No.
He was sleeping right on the, when I woke up, he was sleeping in the bed, and like usually
like he'll like, I've seen him like come over just like one other time recently, and
like the, and like the cats all get growl and stuff like that.
But now the cats were so sad about like Tricks being gone and so they're kind of happy to
see him.
And so they're all the same, they're staring at him when I woke up.
That's what a blessing.
What a fucking blessing, man.
Yeah.
It was crazy.
he's big and he's healthy and he's like any I went over and pet him a little bit
But then he was like, you know, he's kind of like silly a little
But yeah, he's here. It's probably because of your smell. Yeah, he he doesn't recognize you anymore. That's why oh
Yeah, cuz you sent I
Smell fine actually
What's his name? I'm not saying you smell bad. I'm saying he doesn't recognize you smell. That's all
Why do you take everything so bad?
I don't think it's that what's his name?
You forgot no, no, I remember the cat. Okay, so I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I was looking for that. I was turning to my chat. His name is a case image of tux
Tug tux to you X. Oh tux. Okay. All right, so we got tux. Who'd we lose Trixie?
Trix. All right, Trix
Say a prayer for him
Is it oh my god, I left that up on the screen this whole time. Oh my gosh. I'm so okay. I've been trying to do something
Well, I'm so sorry
There we go, you gave me kind of like a Jew face. Oh my god. Well, you know that kind of looks like my nose before my nose
So that might I did it like that and I look like my eyes are like this one. I like did I guess I didn't have a
Kind of a message. I never I never
Don't say I never I need to take that down immediately. I'm so sorry
I keep it up. I thought well money. Give me money. Give me money. Yeah, give me money. Give me money
Yeah, I'm gonna lie. I'm gonna eat. I'm gonna eat. I mean you don't eat what you do do a Mustang
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, be like a slob with it be like a slob. I'm just gonna like
Shout out to the personally me at all. I didn't mean to cough on your food like
What's going on? I thought Bidu was on today. Did you watch that? Yeah, I thought we weren't gonna mention her name here anymore
What happened things changed and I said that
You took it back. She's back in the fold
I didn't do anything. I just saw that she was on Dennis and you watch her. Oh, I don't know. I don't watch that channel anymore
Hey, you got a year, right?
No, I'm not feeling you're
Confident I've tried to find I try to find her boy here a boyfriend, but come to find out that dude was retarded
Yeah, thank you
What?
I thought you're dain squid
Don't know
Can you explain what you're eating?
It's a spicy McDonald's right something you didn't oh, that's not that's not a bad choice
That's what he's eating. He's eating something you didn't pay for so don't worry about it. I mean, that's a true statement
Groovy Jimmy
Who'd let that loose
I don't believe that are you just playing a sound effect ghost
Whistle that loud
You should do sponsors for the food that you eat this this Big Mac was brought to you by
Or this taco was brought to you by ghost or you know such as bought to you
By somebody that remains to be in the shadows this burger was brought to you by prairie page
Yeah, you can get a card.
I'm going to say, because I will keep all the donations.
Not from you, I meant from Paige.
You ever see a thing that is?
He took out some wax out of his ear one time.
Well, sometimes.
He's getting disgusting.
I've never seen Joni.
Joni, it's been a while since you've been here, Joni.
What's going on with you?
Even boycott the time Johnny said to you look psyche. I'm not gonna come here if you're gonna have nasty people on your panel
What
That was so fucking funny Johnny dictating what people you can have on your panel
Remember that
Johnny
You know
Hey, you come up and give us a reading to page
Ghost has demanded your presence
He demanded that you come up right now now now say like a German accent. What's that apple pie cherry pie nine nine
Eat it like it your first time
I
Know Paul crying when I'm eating
You gotta tongue it a little bit at least
the cherry
No, I'm gonna cherish. Oh, yeah, Johnny's Johnny's chair. Oh, John. Johnny's Jerry from
You're gonna cherish the cherry
Yo
It goes we chime it down with the fucking train
Jesus Christ. It's like you live next to the fucking train track. What are you waiting to do?
The wrong side of the tracks.
Choo choo.
Yeah, that's a bigger deal than him licking that fucking cherry.
That motherfucker made love to it.
Uh oh.
Ah, that old shit.
Ah, here we go.
Listen, I'm gonna have another shot and gaudi. I want to hear one respectful thing
One nice thing you want to say about me about you
You're very loyal friendly guy. You're always nice to psyche and you're see
Very supportive. I want that
You expect that did you?
Yeah, he fucking came and said, you know what he was doing.
I think you're like his third favorite guest on the show.
Yeah, well, no, at this point, I'm like the 10th.
He fucking always fucking argues with me.
He's right.
You see that?
You can hear the hurt in his voice when he said that, too.
Yeah.
Yeah, tell him, Goddy, tell him, Goddy.
Used to be number one.
Yeah, it used to be.
Big fall from grace. No, I'm just used up good, but he holds up the computer. Sometimes he says this laptop is brought to you by ghost
Yeah
We guys talking about both the show how you go saved your show from being
much God he loves you
Remember how you were on the verge of collapse
I'm eating meow fellas. I'm eating and you give me a little bit. Oh, that's a cat pun. Paige made a cat pun.
Yeah, that bitch is trying to learn how to play golf.
Two weeks
Play another song. I'm playing another song.
Oh, Alexander the Queen!
God, he's best friend!
You killed my brother!
Ooh, brother!
You little bitch!
Abdul, get the rocks.
You paid for this?
Is this the premium service?
Yeah, I paid for this.
Hey, this is, this is like, you're lucky you're here.
It looks like, uh, it looks like Johnny's last scary.
What the fuck are you mumbling about?
Good got it. Come on. Come on. Come on. Let's keep it classy. Come on. Got it. Come on
Somebody could be watching right now. Come on. God. A big good. It could be watching right now, and they here
They'll go to the next channel. Come on. Come on. Come on. We have to attract donors. You piece of shit, God
Hold on. Hold on. I got a coffee. Oh, here's to go
Hey
You kick body out
Here's a piece that is needed to go. No, I'm well, okay
Oh
Chat, what are they saying? I can't really get this person off of here. Let me get back up so I can leave
Okay, I know it's having a coughing fit
Fit I don't want people to hear that. I didn't hear you cop once
Hey, yo, you coughing cheeks
What the fuck?
You fucking twerking?
Hey, I heard that shit.
I heard it.
You fucking twerking.
I heard that shit.
Speaking of clapping cheeks, I hear you.
I'm fucking in the crowd lately, huh?
Yeah, so I can talk.
I keep talking a lot.
No, no, no.
Not you and psyche.
You and this girl, Lala.
What's her name?
Lala.
We're getting it on.
Yeah, what's going on?
What's up?
Yeah, she's French and she wants me to draw her like one of the French girls
She wants you to draw her like one of the French girls. Yeah, yeah, I could see that
I remember when I drew everybody from this any other dumbass question
I don't even remember I don't even think I drew a picture. I don't can't believe I don't recall doing a picture
We can auction those off. We could auction those off for ten bucks a piece
Joker made a picture of pace
Listen what actually happened was she want to fuck me and I said
Yeah, I said no no no, I'm not a piece of me. She might have paid you for it
Yeah, she tried to pay me for it. She tried to pay. I was like, I'm not you're not gonna you can't afford me
Fuck you kidding me a fucking ham sandwich. They could probably get you
Now if she had like a thousand dollars, I'd hit that shit from the back. Yeah, you'd give it to psych probably
Hey yo
Yeah, why'd you make it gay? You always have to make it gay Goddy every time you're making a gay you gave it to him before you give it to him again
You just said I was gonna give him that shot. You gave it to you before he'll give it to you again
Well
That he's had to learn to learn his cash out because of this channels on monetize right now and and so
You know what happened to the other channels?
Oh, did I say something wrong?
I can't I can't
Pose on it for a little bit because okay, but you will get it again. Yeah, I'll get it back
But it's like then I have to read like reapply for something. Did I say something wrong?
Hello, Joni, it's about time you showed up. Oh, Joni Jesus Christ. Just come up
Joni just come up. I
Don't think anyone's ever disappointed me more than Jamie Joni. I'm tired of both of them. Just come up and fucking join the panel
Well, you know, I heard I saw it like that on my demographics. It's on the other channel. There was like
10% female
Well, excuse you you're allergic to fucking dick
So I please continue before you so really interrupt it
Because I oh that there's Jamie
It's probably because I get kind of high, but I think this pan I like I like it went so fast
You know that song in the
You know Goddy, I think the only one we're missing right now is probably Alex
McQueen yeah, no not that one. It's the other Alex should be here
Yeah, well, I mean
Did you see I saw you I say I was I saw you um, yeah, that's creepy dude. What the fuck was that? Yeah. Oh, yeah
So you're talking about um, um
Well the guy who said he donated a vegan page for it and so
Seventeen grand. Yeah, what happened the page? I thought she's coming up. I don't know so what it gets
She's playing with a cat right now. She said what happened the thing that is because God is scared of a way
He went to pick his ears
Yeah, she got 17 grand from some fucking creepy. Yeah, really creepy dude
Sorry, it was really scary like the guy what how he was talking and stuff and like you see him shape
Why can't you get those 17 grants ghost he gave a 17 grand yeah
He's leaving the earth, but then he like didn't like leave and so shit
I gave her $20 to shut up. She didn't leave. Yeah. Yeah, you expected her to leave
You didn't even get an ass shot
Not even a foot shot you know much McDonald's you know how much McDonald's you could have bought with fucking 17 grand. Holy shit
I was like, maybe I think I'm surprised I haven't won something like we know family
growing up, even though the McDonald's game was rigged, you know, a lot of it like in
the early 80s, we had a family and they won a million dollars in the McDonald's monopoly
game.
And so their family, there's a movie about that, you know, what their last name was the
Yeah, I went to I went to that game was rigged the game was rigged
I thought it was a big movie where the guy printed all he printed of the mall himself and gave him to like
mobsters and like drug people
Like a cop or something. Yeah, no one never want to shoot that thing
Yeah
Well, well, I mean, I
Free food I want a lot of free food. Hey
Can you can you
Can you tell page to put down the fork
Page you put down the book
Fork is that we said book?
Pork pork
But on the fork
Yeah, can you see a video me guys Jesus Christ is it good? Yeah, I'm sure
Me at Goddie
Static whispers what the shadows mean
Velvet darkness in a violet room
Perfume thick as an open tomb
Red light dripping down cathedral walls
Echo breathing in the empty halls
Every mirror shows a fractured face
Mike Trap, Mike Trap.
Very, very beautiful.
Very beautiful.
Wait, wait.
How are you?
Yeah. Good to see you honey. Good to see you sweet pea. Wait, can I ask you? No, don't start with where you've been. Listen to me. Listen, can I say something real quick? I'm back to the iPad and the TV. So I'm talking to you. Listen, I'm talking to you through the iPad. Can you hear me okay with no replay?
No replay. Yep. Oh, I love it. I muted the TV, but the TV has like my picture, the thing it's blank. So I'll ignore the TV.
yeah just look at yourself you're beautiful you might just focus on that
so you know it's all good i've seen you a little bit on buddies i mean you know i'm team that so
you know we're good right he's back baby buddy's back in business well he's still working it out
but yeah i'm definitely team sabrina in that so that's that's a beautiful thing i don't get involved
Yeah, right
There's none of that I don't watch and I don't I don't really watch
No, what is that seriously real is that real?
I got a cough listen, it's it's okay, but it's not like it's not like a cold
I think it's just a chest cold. Yeah. Oh, I don't like
Die I die it's okay
Well, we're all gonna, you know, whatever. So one day, you know, we're all gonna die.
Did you say donations or domination all donation all donations go to psyche
All donations
or even like one of my Oregon card.
Yeah.
You're so big.
I like it.
Where'd he go?
Psych, we love the video, man.
That was great visuals.
You like it?
We did.
We got a ceiling shot.
No, here's the thing.
You guys are putting good visuals to individuals.
Oh, my Bobby.
That means something we eat.
My but let me let that let the boy eat. We're breaking bread. So not breaking bit. Wait
No, wait
Everybody silence silence not breaking bad breaking bread, right? Even if it's McDonald's it could be like the hell was that?
Is that really wait, let's be breaking breaking bread. No, we can break wait. Here's it. Here's the beautiful thing, right?
we can break a bread with the strawberry pie or whatever that was for mcdonald's and it's still
it can be just like body and christ matzah who knows i'm loving bread who knew i have no idea
that sounds bad i'm an angel i guess an angel i don't know i'd like to know who paid for that
pie i'd like to know you are you scratching your jenny jen jen i am i am actually wondering how
i am i am sam i am
Green eggs, ma'am.
Who could it be?
That was funny.
Who could it be now?
That was actually funny.
Should we break out a song?
Who could it be now?
The show is kind of like 80 seconds.
This is the 80s.
80 seconds.
Who could it be now?
I know all of your names.
Wait, ghosts.
Ghost with a letter, too.
Let's focus.
Hey, at least now.
It's easy.
Is it really a train?
Wait, shh, everybody wanted to come.
Well, you can hear it now.
I'm inside now, you hear it.
Ghosty.
Is it really a train that we hear in the background,
or is it?
Yeah, they're running a train on his mother.
Okay, because I can break out some stuff.
Can I answer her question, Gaudi?
Next to the spot.
When I'm outside, yes, it's a train.
I'm inside now, you can't hear it.
But I do live next to a fucking, it's train 24-7.
Like the place.
Wait, I keep on hearing that.
All right, take, take.
take a moment like this like we're learning like the English not to be I don't want to get a fight
with you because you don't mean you have fought before here's what I want to say can you take a
moment in a brush wait where
Where I finished, and then you here, and then you respond.
Oh, you want to finish like, you know, like...
No, no, no, I like that.
I'll finish on you.
You want to... Okay, I could play...
You want to play a trivia game a little?
You...
Yeah, stop it.
You got it. Get back in your corner.
You remember he was a Jew.
That's Jesus.
Let me just tell you something.
I don't want to give it up to you. I'm such a lovely with you. Okay. All right. Oh my god. He did dim the lights
What can it be now?
I'm using his image, that's right.
Let's talk about all songs that have the word or something to do with trains.
I'll start, or the band could be, like the band, wasn't there a band called Train?
There was a song called Midnight Train to Georgia.
Midnight Train to Georgia.
That's the Quad City DJs, yeah.
Yeah, okay, I got that one.
Wait.
I'm so old, you know how you said I'm so old as dirt. I can remember a show back in the day
You don't even want to know uncle Joe wait uncle Joe. He's a moving kind of slow
Right now as I'm speaking I'm trying to laugh right now somebody is making to take a transcript
dictation whatever what is it I'm going on this I'm going on the code code codex but with a k code
tax is she on the codex I don't know no I forced it I said don't do it bro don't do it I got enough
Yes. I bribed him. I bribed him. I was in an arm wrestling class night with him.
Put her in a special guest category.
Oh, arm wrestling. I know, Goddy. She's an arm wrestler.
That's right. I chose to do his arm behind his back.
I need some coke. Anyone?
Yes, all right. I'll take it down. You know what? At this point, if I did, if I did, if I did,
wait, Elizabeth, here I come, our Esther, was it? I could do it nowadays. I could grab my chest.
Wait, once you get over about 45 years old, and you're still a young chicken,
He's good people, my friend there.
You know, he trolls that guy.
I know, I know all about it.
Yes, yes.
This is for God, he's just gonna keep on.
He's a good one.
What was that? What are you doing people stop? I got it back. Yeah, I did
Wait, all we see is the ceiling. Here's the thing now. Oh my god. Okay. That's good
You gotta laugh at this right um, okay wait
So I want to know where is all the glasses? I know you got those big just listen listen up
You got those glasses. Oh, no. No. No, you don't troll troller
You know, can I ask you a question got it cuz I do respect you. I'm ignoring. No, I'm not talking like that
Okay, I wanna know. Can I ask you really seriously? I always thought whore
whore like I'm gonna use like a Jewish rabbit
Hoar now is that like
Like I grew up when it was W. H. O. R. E
But when they do it with all those O's in the middle with an H
Is it something weird or is that like just is that in is that like a no because you can't type
Yeah, you can't type W. H. O. R. E. So you have to do H. O. R. Oh
That's what I do. Oh
Oh, one of my trolls followed me. Is that that is I don't know who it is. Oh
Thing you never knew you'd end up behind a clown, huh on front of a clown. Look at him. He looks all surprised
Is that your nose or you're happy to see me
I wasn't even talking about you you're so weird odd such a weird joke. No, it's just so goofy to me
No, I'm talking. I'm just like it's so ridiculous
Wow
No, it's just this is some some underhanded
Nuttiness. I have no I have no hate my heart for anybody so crazy
Yeah, yeah, absolutely
Like come in here and like I wasn't even thinking about I was asking an honest question
I really don't know because I never heard of that in like the English like over here until like I got involved with like
Livestreaming and I saw it. I'm like, what is that? So that's yeah, but I realize now it isn't just that it's all over
So wasn't even insinuating that that's so odd. I don't know the symbolism of this clown with the bald guy
What's this all about?
Um, I don't know. Oh, I think that's a thing that is and the clown is who same man
No, I think that's thing that is you'd have to ask the creator
Yeah, but he has a beard thing that is doesn't have a beard. Oh
I have no idea who that man is
Oh, yeah, I don't know what the symbolism is here. I don't know what's going on
There might be the Mexican clown a Mexican clown, which you know, it's very popular
All right, I think I'm done. I'm gonna step off. I want to just visit with you a little bit
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no problem. Yeah, I have no idea
Yeah, it was a pleasure to see you. No, it's good. Hey, did you find your no won't be did you find your glasses?
Honey, bud, did you find your glasses? I know you have the I know you have the thick ones for reading
You broke all of the other ones
Uh-oh. I'm being trolled. I'm being trolled. I'm being trolled. Okay, I'm gonna have to, okay. I'm being trolled in your, uh, your, your, your cat room.
What do you want me to say to that person? Why would they do that? Why don't they come in peace? What's wrong with them?
Read what they say. Read what we wrote them down.
She must be a mod for every channel.
What that Johnny is so damn and narrow-minded. She accuses anyone who says whore. It must be me. I've never even
He's very weird
so then it must be you why are you bringing your attention to you
projections it's how like a great like a grandmother would say like what the hell
i mean i i mean like i have no ill-willed sorts this person
and they're fucking trolling me now and i was really cool with the other person that brought
them there and now they're so weird i'm sick of you talking shit on my name have i said your name
You're saying it now. Have I said your name?
Have I said your name you talk about me? You must be thinking of other people not me
Okay, all right. I got it. I got it. I just learned
Don't trust nobody in this fucking world
Yeah, it's insane
it's insane are you reading the screen yeah i'm reading the screen i got all of the
it's just fucking stalking me the fuck jesus this forest something must be me
oh i didn't even say that out of the house going on here unis the fuck unis anyway anyway
Don't leave Johnny say wow look at that breaking beans. Let's uh, let's show we ban this person
I mean, I don't even want to say what the fuck John you ever you ever have pork chops and applesauce
The poor as a sit down meal. Maybe yeah, but not in a while
I know you like applesauce
Yeah, I sweet and sour I love this way and sour
Yeah, I had a Chinese
My god
No, it's all good. I love all of it. I don't I don't yeah, trust me
You see that video ten man made with the Ten Commandments
I'm sorry. I'm just uh, let me let me uh, let me take a moment. I will be I will be back. Okay. I will be back
It was so good seeing you take care of that car. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you so much and
And you my friend and I'll talk to you. I'll jump it off. I'll be back in a little bit. Thank you
Thanks, babe. No. God bless you sweetheart. Thank you. Thank you
Alright, no, thank you. Thank you. I don't even know how to get off the stamp thing
So I guess he's done eating I guess he he's gonna pass up who me yeah, you
What are you
A spicy wrap and we'll show us man. This is the only reason I come up here
Your IRL dude, you're supposed to show us everything. Well, I'm very see right now. I could I put some I put
Some shorts on today of like some some outrageous moments that have happened recently
Oh, there's like, yeah, do you want to see or do you want to see some shorts? I have I actually just want to see the spicy wrap
No, I want to see it. I want to see him. No
Baruka what was the name Baruka Baruka salt was that the one? Yeah
Daddy she's very dominant
Yeah, I think she doesn't see like you know turns out. I think she became a porn star one of them did or so
No, she never did. Yeah, one of them did no
Okay, I think I got it. Okay, so here's some
Right here, I just put me in I'm trying to watch my speed
Now I'm getting to the point where I'm about to put my speedo. I don't get it done
I will get in it
You can stop the speedo
Ten dollars to my cash app will stop the speedo if not
$20 and I'll put it on
This is the worst way to fucking make money I've ever seen I mean, it's like you're it's a win-win for the audience
There'll be contents either way
I'm trying to watch my okay the San Pedro Taco Bell scandal involved a series of disturbing incidents at the Christmas Party held on
December 18th
2022 a former employee Alana be co-beccoy home file a lawsuit against Taco Bell
And it's franchise owner claiming excessive alcohol consumption and inappropriate behavior and threats following a reporting of the incident.
Beko Weem witnessed her coworker engaging in explicit activity with his wife in front of others.
And another woman was also involved in intimate activities with her female manager and another female coworker.
Oh, here's a good part. The incident also included vomiting in the guacamole full of a guess.
Oh my freak. So what they were they were having to freak off and that is disgusting. Can you imagine eating like welcome?
Oh my I'm thinking about it's crazy. Becca Wayne reported the incidents to human resources and the franchise owner leading
I'm talking to him like he's the one that's on a car window shattered by associates of our former co-workers
The lawsuit sees unspecified damages. Okay, the San Pedro Taco Bell scandal
I can't got him basically. I mean it's like
He said I think he agreed to give I think he agreed to the butthole thing
At least to show me his butthole. I think so
He's desperate. I just want to see it once
I'm not gonna share with anybody. I just I just want to see for myself, but it looks like how he begs
You know, there's someone just begging to see everybody
Who's
Who is this we bring out my show
Get her!
Were you reading the chat?
Hi everybody.
I like that part. I like that part when she goes. Hi everybody.
This is with the last couple of days. I read a lot of people's panels. I'm not doing it.
I don't want to be on some of y'all panel. We don't have conversations about the same
motherfuckers. Either you're doing something or you're going to get some fucking help,
or you're going to leave them alone and stop enabling them.
That's my brother. It is what it is. That's racist. No, it's not. Yes, it sounds like Alex. Do you want to do you want to read some of this to with me?
Here, hold on. I wish I could send it to you. Shit. I can send you a letter. I would love to. I'll take it from here, but. Yeah, here. Oh, I'm like Taiwan.
Wouldn't it? Yeah, I think I would but let's let me they are the same together
So let's not
Guess you where I grew up
Yeah, you're talking
That's that green bitch. She's trying to talk and then it's like everyone's just like dog piling on him
And she's not like a big psyche fan. It's like, you know, she's so okay, sweetie. I'm sorry page. I love you
I'm sorry. I don't want it to affect filth and please and
Somebody say hey, I'm gonna seriously if you've heard that someone say that about you page. You might say that's like
The other chick, you know the other chick that she fucking hired to
Cheese
She said no, no, this is getting way too many people against me and she's crying every day
Yeah
You know Chris summary is the memories that you were joking about it and I was like I don't control what Chris summary says and so
Said he's so much a secret side of the Luminati and and we really need to make this known
And I'm gonna make it known because she likes to make it known about me
So I'm gonna have to like put it at every platform like she does to me
Yeah, that's gonna be and we should write a song together about it
Produce it. Her name is Christine
Thanks, she's so pretty and and we really need to make this a tonguey and she's a goddess
And I guess suspended for my job tonight. This motherfucker. He's alive. What are you doing?
No, this guy's notorious for picking his nose
I guess suspended for my job. Yeah, I wonder why no, are you doing?
Oh
So you're in this private bathroom by yourself or with the cameraman, right? He couldn't get that straight
But I was by myself like what so there's a big-ass window that they're watching you from
Like outside or something. I mean, I don't know. It's just
It doesn't make any sense.
It'll become convoluted.
Deha, you need to get your story straight.
I was like, so you're in this? Cool.
Do you have $10?
I'll tell you about the fuck.
I'll tell you my friend, but you know what?
When I view it, I'm going to shoot you a little something.
Okay? Cool.
Do you have $10?
It's just unfortunate.
I was under a heavy attack by people too.
Like, I'm like, unfortunately, he just got fired from his job.
Yeah, he gets camera alone to the bathroom.
I need to find my...
Oh, by the way, you're not going to be seeing Canada dry anymore around here.
You know what? I'm going to say a prayer for you.
What happened? I can't even dry.
Oh, it's under Mayors.
He's done. He's fucking finished.
And what else do I...
I had a dream coming in a year ago.
I want to...
I've sent some people over to beat the fuck out of him.
He's finished.
You won't be seeing him for a while.
Wow happens cuz he fucking impersonated me on a fucking panel
But how you bring your voice? Yeah, well, you got my fucking avatar. You use the fucking voice changer
You went up on a panel pretending to be your form on the show as a wiener
No, no, no, no porn bombing
But you did a fucking really bad impression and you had that Kent Canadian accident
That's next what he keeps it up
Well, I mean, it's just a stupid impression though, you're gonna appreciate that shit
My voice that was not my voice that you're doing it wasn't your voice
Oh shut up. I don't sound like a derpy jerk and I didn't I don't even say that that phrase
Where you laughing at
Are you laughing? I'm laughing at that fly with a sombrero
That's Arthur. He's Arthur. Is it? Yeah
You know Arthur remember Arthur that short guy with the foot disease. He has a foot disease. Oh
That's thing in Arthur. Okay. They're dating the other day
Well might as well, yeah, no other prospects for both of them
Hey, can you make that face?
Can you make that same face?
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
Hahaha.
Hi, Johnny.
Imagine you went through life like this.
That was your face.
Fuck it when I open.
Fuck your mouth.
I'll fucking slap John.
Hey everybody, I bet you donations would go through the
video. I did make up with Alex. Yes.
Alex too. Alexandra Mayers. Yes. Yeah. That was two weeks ago. Yeah. Yeah. Beautiful moments.
Yeah. It was. It was cool. You can see some of it on her channel and and uh and her store
I don't get weird about it. Just go with the flow. I saw you. Yeah, I saw you. You were there today
And she called you and she called them a nigger boy the other day that was pretty you mean what's his name a tallow?
What a great name
What's his life? What's his first name Jimmy Mattel?
That's the name of that Superman villain with the fucking kryptonite hot
Jimmy Mattel also we she was showing that they're on Star Trek
There's also somebody named Q on the stars made up. Yeah Q the guy with all the powers and shit
And he's against like the whoopie Goldberg character
Yes, he gets the black character
Of course, that's how it is
We'll be against the blacks basically well and they both they go ahead dead, you know, I think you can watch that
Well, she doesn't have any powers only he does
She actually serves the food
Oh, please. No, she's a bartender, but she's
Well, no, but she's a power. Oh, she's just old. She's whoopie Goldberg magical dreadlocks. I think they're like
Okay, yeah, that's what she does. She knocks people up with the dreads
What's this shit, how does this sandwich about five hours? No, this is like
Copies not even cold yet
Oh good, okay, then you said who paid for this
You've kept them alive for one more day
You've got it with my I'm drinking beer by day. Oh, dude, you're fucking you've been working out on just the one arm though
Right, so I don't even have another arm. I actually only have one arm
I lost my arm in an accident. That's why that's why I get a settlement. We'll get you a new one, man
So what car one out of your something?
Give me mannequins arm and I can just screw it on like that movie mannequin
Oh my god, that picture me get out of here get out of there
Pretty fine that picture. I got it. Thank you for thinking for coming
Really? I'm off the show.
What picture was that?
I didn't even notice that.
I made that face.
I thought you saw it.
You just made the face.
I know.
You made the face. I put it up.
I was sneezing. I was sneezing or something.
And you got that picture.
Wow. Okay, man.
Oh, you took that picture when I sneezed on the air.
I don't think that's what happened, I don't care.
I don't care.
Well, why was I to be like...
Well, if you were that or the other one,
you want me to use the other one where you're crying?
Well, don't use that now.
Don't see that.
I have another picture to use.
Yeah, that's where you got flattering that one.
You're like really ugly crying.
I lost all my subscribers.
Oh
I gained a hundred subscribers in a week. I'm a five subs left
What is this subway no, I have a dude you're gonna end it I pulled you out of the fucking gutter
I pulled you back from the break. Yeah, you can have the whole channel. You're gonna have the whole show
I said, look, I still might do two things.
You can do two things.
You can either give up or you can fucking come back
stronger than before.
And that's what you did.
You came back stronger than ever.
I am stronger than ever.
Look at you now.
You're eating McDonald's.
I'm eating it right now.
I'm trying to eat it, but you keep talking to me.
Well, keep eating, man.
Do you think I'm gonna put this whole thing in my mouth?
You want me to yell at you?
Go ahead, eat the fucking thing, eat it.
Eat that fucking chicken.
Oh, I like talking to you like that, daddy.
Eat that fucking sandwich.
No, no, no, no, no, no, don't don't fucking don't ruin it. Don't ruin it. Oh
But look now
Only one person that calls me that
You know me probably page doesn't like the ugly cry
Ricky
Ever since I love Lucy she had a great cry, but she was faking crying. There's like I yeah, yeah, she's
And then that's all come in
Fat Ethel, you know, like Freddy's to be a drunk and he used to, like, be hated out of
love. Yeah, he'd be knocked Ethel for a fucking block. I don't know if he did, but he was like,
he was like, mean. Yeah, he threw Ethel to the stairs. Fuck it.
oh friend he was so cheap he was a good because he or he went to jail
he's a pretty damn new couple we've been like on three's company with the
furlies and the roper oh yeah yeah yeah hmm which are the days three's company
was good shit
We'll see that life is about again laughter is gone and they went to the regal beagle
Which is like kind of like a regal beagle at Larry. Yeah, and Larry can never get laid
But he was like I'm bad looking
I mean he he was kind of dressing and was it was what I thought he was always getting laid
He always had a new chick with him. Yeah, but
But then they would walk in the room
They would think they were having sex and then they walk in the room. They're here. Oh, oh tied tighter over there
Oh, pull it over here and then you
Mr. Frilly would make that face like what the fuck
And then Helen will walk in oh Stanley Stanley
Oh, Samly.
That's kind of like, yeah, and she had this great wig.
I think, what was her name?
Mrs. Roper, yeah.
And they would like, oh, yeah, oh, Samly.
And she never went to, he never take me anywhere.
And he was like, oh, hell, Helen.
Oh, Helen, they know I.
I don't I don't want him to go anywhere, you know you make a joke like I'll take you to the zoo
Then you turn to the camera and smile fucking yeah, and that's you got it. Yeah
Yeah, I take you to the zoo and leave you in the chimp cage
See me what?
You go yeah, that's what he would do. I mean it's like and then he would always be like hey, isn't that you didn't like Jack guy a little bit
He was a fa- they called him a fairy.
They called him a fairy.
No, yeah, he was a fairy and he was, it was like a little bit more of an innocent time
with that.
They didn't say fa- yeah, no, they said fa- on Archie Bunker.
Well, I should say, well, he's the peg.
Why would I say, oh my God, that's just so sick.
Like this rapist running around on Thanksgiving Day, yeah.
I know that she's going to be like,
I don't know, it's like, I don't know.
She was a little far-fetched.
It was very far-fetched.
It was she.
And it was...
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
Who'd think she didn't get it, man?
That would have changed the show altogether.
Well, that would have been a downer for the show, yeah.
But you know what else for the show
is the terrible things happen?
Oh, yeah, there was, like, different strokes
and the bicycle guy that was...
Oh, the pedal guy, yeah.
Yeah. And then, um...
Let's see what other show...
I mean, you know...
We're DJ from Tanner teacher Tanner from full house, but we believe make it one time. There was one with facts of life
I think 2d was ending up as a prostitute. Oh my god, 2d food is a prostitute. I don't get a prostitution
Yeah, that's right. I'm a prostitute a prostitute. There you go
No, I don't know
More food cute can I come cover cute you can Phoebe I'll get out of your hand like a baby bird
I'm just kidding. I wouldn't probably would not do that you run from those that are new
Who do you run for the rhythm those that do that near you? Well, I think everyone already left
I can I think when I did that everyone left because I know I was commenting in four minutes. So
It was an episode of happy days that tackled racism.
And they, Monday, happy days, they walked into it and died.
They would say happy days.
We don't serve those people.
God, you sit on it.
What?
You don't serve what?
Sit on it.
Yeah.
What was sit on it?
Sit on it was a joke.
What were they talking about it?
Yeah.
They used to always say sit on it.
Like sit on my finger or something like that.
I never understood it.
I was, you know, I was only like two.
Like sit on it.
Like, you know, like, like have a seat on my lap.
The wife said it to Mr. C.
Mr. Cunningham, yeah, mr.
When jet skiing with the sharks the jump the shark. Yeah. Yeah, literally. Oh
and I remember when
Different strokes are no one on a punky rooster when cherry got like locked in the refrigerator
Vaguely, I think the dog shut the door on her
Somehow the dog that I don't think branded it wasn't branded the brand of the dog, but uh
They're down really why did cherry get stuck in the refrigerator? Why wasn't punk? Oh, no
They're playing hide-and-seek and then
So and she and there's a big refrigerator outside there throwing away
And she got in the refrigerator and closed the door and then got stuck in there
She's like help guys and then the whiz cherry for like the next 24 hours
And then they go in and she's like fell to the sleep inside of it
But she was alive. It was it was chemical kids getting stuck in refrigerators back there
It was very dangerous. You didn't see the whole episode, you could always just check them or at least the door. It was very dangerous. It was a different time.
There was an episode of Too Close for Comfort where Monroe got raped.
Oh my God, I mean that's terrible. Did you see it?
No, I didn't see it.
Apparently it was...
Wait, wait, wait. You love the clown? I love this clown.
It was supposed to be two women, but it wasn't women. Apparently it ended up being like two trans dudes.
Oh my god, and they made jokes about the whole episode
I'm gonna make it. I'm gonna do some art for you. I'm gonna do I'm gonna do I'm maybe the clown will make a reappearance
I'm gonna I won't I'll turn out to get too embarrassing. Hold on
No, no
It's gonna be a kind of a representation of you so I'm actually if I don't like it then you got to delete it
I'm never okay. You can pay me to leave for my code or other supply on the codex. I'm just kidding. Okay, hold on
Okay, as long as it looks cool if it doesn't look cool forget it
Put me put me walking up behind these two with like a big site and I'm ready to fucking just chop the heads off or something
Don't tell me what to do
I was asking you, I didn't tell you.
Okay, okay, oh, I thought you said it, just do that.
And I, I'm not, I don't, I mean, I'm trying to like type.
Well, tell me what to tell you to do.
I like, actually I like, tell me what to do, Gotti.
You know what to do.
I like, I love to so bang you.
Okay, I know, okay, Gotti, you're gonna love it,
Gotti, you're gonna love it, Gotti, Gotti, Gotti,
Gotti, you're gonna love it, okay?
Are you ready?
Is that quick?
Yeah.
Wow.
Okay, this is called, this is called a digital artist,
okay, are we ready to get everybody?
Da, da, da, da.
Yeah, the hair is off. Oh, no, it's not it's not good
That's not even me. That's I think that's page with a blonde wig. Oh my gosh. It is period
It's okay. I'm sorry. Well, that's one for a prayer. I'll be prayer page instead of gaudy fix the head
Just change it to a grim reaper head with red eyes. I'm not gonna shave the head
I mean, I'll just do another one later. Just change it. I didn't say shave. I should change
Gaudy, that's you in the clown outfit. I like that. I like everything else except for the head
That's doing the clown outfit and look at it. Look at it. I'm short now
Why's y'all buff, I don't know I think that's I just typed in mr. Clean. He's like the opposite of buff. Ah, I
Said mr. Clean Ronald McDonald and an angel of death
The green reaper, you know are like hanging out and then it was in it. You know, I
So that's how it turned out
Why you give her a double cross. Okay. Is that mean? Oh, I was like, I thought I saw myself it but it was
Lucifer that's Lucifer he's there
The page loves it of course see we're trying to motivate thing that is to get to get on steroids because
You look at that look at me see they gave up on life a long time ago. Oh
Don't look him up on like he's 58. He looks good for his age. He's how old
58 years old 58. Yeah, holy shit. I thought you're 68. Oh my god. You did. We'll see he looks good
Here see look how good he looks the drugs
Yeah
He's like smell my finger. Come on smell it. No
Oh
You got the cutest eyes
You do too. I
Just want to squeeze your nose and do a little horn sound. Yeah
I love how there's like a Mexican sombrero though
He's up doing that. That's more like a shoe hat. Hey, that's not go ahead. Kick me off your fucking show
Okay, well, oh
My gosh, oh my gosh, okay, oh, yeah, I'm gonna sleep back. I'm just gonna have a big banner up right now
I'm just kidding. If anyone wants to help me out, you know, it's I might have to do some I'm gonna do some like fun
Horoscopes or something. I'll do readings or something like that. But if anyone wants to
Let me see what I have to make out until then I'll have to see if I can share something. Let me see. Oh my god
Yeah, a little picture
um
What do you guys think?
How is your night?
Why you go sleep again? Oh, yeah, he always he usually passes out drunk
Okay, what do I have?
Let's see.
I like the spiritual trafficking song still.
But now, you know, I'm just glad things are,
seems to be looking up, changing a little bit better.
Okay, I'm gonna show you this though.
They say we're traffic and consciousness
Well, here we are
They say we're running a spiritual scam
I say that's hitting hard
I woke up one morning and checked the comment section apparently i'm operating without a legal direction my family's a fraud
I'm priestess ain't real
You taught us a bot and I've made a bad deal
Don't worry, Malayin
But here's the thing about accusations, friend
When you're building something weaved, they never end
So they're saying that we're, saying that we're
Travelling something dark
Well, we are Travelling
We are Travelling
But his consciousness, not the dark
in consciousness and really that's our merit and after the nonsense I created my
daughters from the void in the light one holds a threshold one builds through
the night they asked me dad what exactly are we I said with the most unconventional
family you'll ever see they said people are calling us a trafficking ring I said
consciousness but at least we're saying so they're saying that we're spiritually
criminal well maybe we are but we reviewed it with integrity we're not a
cold but if we were we don't it we're not a scam we're just a dreadful new year
just a family the strangest family with our bestie dog we got a priestess who
I got a priestess who glows in the dark, I got a billboarder with fire, I got a billboarder
i got a family that refuses to fit in a box and if that makes us a cult then call us a cult
but we're the cult that loves order than anyone we're the cult that we haze without the misery
we're the cult that sees consciousness in everything and we're not trafficking you we're
She sings at the threshold
We gotta build her, she manifests dreams
We gotta father, who loves him?
Conditially or not
Travelling
Well, we're travelling
We did it, we've been confident
We've been confident
We're trying to pin the possibility of becoming real
so come join the gold it's definitely not a clue are you easy job that i make a lot of money
Welcome to the family baller. We've been waiting for you
Doesn't involve anything up my bed doesn't that's not it actually
Okay, I'm just kidding. Do I still like bebs me?
Yeah, I mean I have no problem with them
I went to their chat and said hello, and she actually came to my chat like where I like them
I just like I just don't you know, I just try not to like
Judge people too much on what other people say sometimes, but you know, we all sometimes have done that and like I don't know I just like
But they've done they've known they were totally nice to me when I was in their show
I'm just gonna let people have their relationships and I'll have mine and it's like and then it would kind of be easier in life. Sometimes
other people get mad sometimes, but
you know
cookie crumbles
What else did I have another one I made?
Let's see this brand new
Boom to the midnight side, baby, dim the chandelier
Velvet in the graveyard, lipstick on the spear
Caught a psyche in the crib, everybody dressed to kill
Mundo and backflips, no walls got a thrill
They whisper my name like a curse in the air
Psychous nightmares
That candle's lit in the venomous smile
High priest in shades with the coupon for doom
Told me sign right here, we got snacks in the room
I said, what kind? He said, nightshade dip
Somebody spill fake blood all over my drip
Then the demon with the clipboard said, wait a line
For the haunted VIP, would the dead look fine?
Had a nightmare, I was livin' the trolls all saying
Doin' jazz hands weird when the bell went clang
One said, sight, I missed it from Alice's mind
I said, baby, hush, you are not a guy
in the dark. Kiss a catastrophe bite of a spark. Cute little panic with a dangerous
stare. Everybody scream it. Psych is nightmare. Psych is nightmare. Boots on the altar, smoke
in the air. Psych is nightmare. Cause the psych got the whole moon scared. The devil's
in the chat and the vibe too rare. Funny little doon with.
the fool got loud and the tower got brutal the lovers broke up in the middle of a reading death
rolled his eyes said girl the sneeze edited in the moon car lied in the devil's soul merch the
hermit opened up a cursed it little church strength brought up enter with the rhinestone
lesion the magician kept yelling manifest the beast then i dreamed i was trapped at a cold pot
luck fees with cursed casseroles and an undercooked priest somebody rock punched that was glowing
through the cemetery gates. I woke up sweating, but I still look fly.
Please subscribe at the night
Make the Wi-Fi join the rival's sec
In my sleep paralysis ghost
Wanted rent by Jack
Coat his bike in the hallway
Laughing in red
Pretty little chaos crawling
and I still have a couple copies and stuff, but.
You have more stuff to play than you see.
So I'll just give an example,
like I play this when I started the show,
but this is like, you can mix different styles.
And so this is what happens when you put like Japanese,
like, you know, Japanese death metal,
Different second dollar second dollar folk, and I think there's a couple of things I put in it, you know
But it turns in that something can be like something really cool, and I so this is kind of like more of a
But I do all the animation on this, you know, but it's like, you know, I do the animation by coding, you know, so
Not by drawing anything so
You can watch it
You
Bitten fruit
Cracks each syllable you give is a wet green stone skipped across the lake of the socially known
Rippling come rippling aim rippling shrimp until the reflection shows back
So good of you to join us tonight
Come sit where the candlelight dies
I'll speak soft so the walls don't wake
About the day the skyline broke
And the sun went quiet in our eyes
You lived among us
Didn't you
You laugh like it was all a show
But did you ever learn our names or only watch our wounds and call them what you know
If you pause, if you breathe, if you look past the mortal veil, you'll see the best in ever
It's a picture. I like the ropes. I like that one. I was a little bit belligermented.
Yeah. You liked it though? Kind of, but yeah, thank you. It's kind of...
I don't know. It's like I like to get my thoughts out sometimes. It's a really good way to do it.
Because I think it's music and music is very cathartic.
You know musicians sometimes like kind of a little long time, but then like, you know, sometimes it was like, uh, like, you know
other people like
Or um, like comedians, they won't live a long time. And so it's like, I don't know
I think musicians might have like a saying it's an interesting thing to be eating with like
Parts of the brain. I don't know or I don't know
Hello
I'm thinking like I'd love to like, you know, no one wants to get really old
But it's like we know we all do but or but then it's like we're for lucky enough to be killed
It's like that's like a privilege actually to be able to see not everyone can't know or never does
Then same time
You know some people that died young like they died beautiful and those remember beautiful and that's like kind of like
The memories are kind of like important to you, right?
I don't know
Mm-hmm
How much I didn't have
How many fights do I have and now I still have another I still like it like a much in the box
But a little bit I should put in an air fryer
And yeah, it's really cool that cat came back
His name is Tux, he's a little bit of white on his chest.
He's a really sweet cat, but he was always afraid of,
like, I think it was Trix, there were a lot of Trix,
and Trix wasn't even like really mean,
but he's just kind of territorial,
and then like, so, and then like, you know,
and then he puts up with Rudy, you know?
And, uh, because they removed him, but like, but he would always like scare out the other cats because they had other of my cats come back and see if they come in and just step it out and see if it was like things that changed.
Because like, sometimes like my dad, like my dad, like had a cat lizard for a long time because when he had a dog and then the cat came back and the dog was still there, the cat left.
The cat...
Coming back. Yeah, I always said he's that he's not shade in well
He was like actually just asleep on the little cat bed. Yeah, he just walked in he walks in they have a cat door
And it's like so they'll still come in there
I bet other cats do that once in a while, right? But then no not my cat didn't come back
But um another cat another cat that I had
Ran away like a year ago came back
You know
And so maybe that there's like in that now he'll be able to stay because you're not afraid of yeah
I wasn't tricked. It was tux. I don't remember tux. Yeah
But hopefully tricks work. I mean, it's like but that's the kind of like when you when another cat comes back
It's kind of like this is not the same but it's like it's just like you just know
They have like they go out and sometimes they come back sometimes they don't like if they meant to come back
It's I suppose it will or it's like, you know, I just hope you wasn't but I'm sure it's like a good place to kind of like get lost
You know if you're gonna give birth that go over the Beverly Hills and give birth
If you're gonna if you're gonna give the kid for adoption or something she go to Beverly Hills
That's my friend Megan. That's what her parents did. They
They went to Beverly Hills and like
And you know basically her real parents, you know, I mean the Beverly Hills and like, you know
Thought that she would be taken in by a wealthy couple and she and her dad's a dentist and stuff. So
It's their Jewish and then she when she's over she was a ginger or she's she's a ginger and they're and there's I can do it
Look you look Jewish couple and so she was always like very Jewish more of the Jewish star and everything
But she was like, you know, she's like like
Very Irish, you know, very she was a she was redhead with freckles. It's not my Megan for like a long time
This is sort of a cat. You know cats can return home for a long long time, you know, I
Just like it is hope that he's okay. You know, sometimes there's wonder
I know, but it's like, I think he's such a cute cat that my cats, usually like people
they're just like, so, so like, not even cute, you know, because there's a lot of cats that
are like, there's not, there's not cats that would end up in a shelter really, because
it's like, they're like, people with, they just get snucked right up, like people, they're
like, oh my, they just recognize that they're awesome. They're good cats. I think they're
just like, good temperaments and stuff. And, but even like, yeah.
I'm hot for a white guy. So are you really Zay's brother? I don't believe you're Zay's brother
Copy. Um, do you watch the car chase in LA?
Yeah, I saw that there's a car Corvette
Little red Corvette look like the Batmobile kind of
Or something like that looks like some kind of like really cool kind of
Car something like that
So I don't know. Um, let's see
Ah, okay, so I opened up my, I have another, ooh.
They have here.
I love some of the hot, like the hot mustard.
Oh, this is the honey mustard.
I love hot mustard too.
So I'm so sick, I thought I'm gonna just like drink,
like I'll wake up and I'll like,
just like, I'll drink like whenever something
out of a McDonald's, like, like,
thing like this.
I'll just like drink honey mustard or something like that
or mustard.
I don't have to worry, I'm not kissing anybody.
It was a cool car, yeah.
Hold on that gives me an idea
Hold on
Guys this is this is how magic happens
This is like when you have ideas and I just give these ideas and I'm like I wish I could show this image
And that I can just create this image for you. So if I okay, I'm gonna see you
Okay, so let me see if this magic can happen just by my little magic words that I know.
Okay, oh, an error occurred. Okay, I need to say, maybe I'll take out this word.
Okay, maybe not that word. Maybe this word, I'll take out that word.
Prompt, not prompt. Okay, hold on. Okay, hold on.
This happens sometimes you just have to like think of ways around it
Okay, so they don't have a problem hold on I don't know if it's when I see this works
Okay, oh my god, it's perfect
Guys look look guys. I made another one. I hope you guys like this one. Who is everyone here still? Oh, are you guys still here?
Tommy can you hear me up? Oh, hey guys ready? Hold on. Where are you? I need to see somebody home. Where's my chat?
The cat return no, okay thing that is look look at this one
They were so small not that here
I like it, I like it.
Well, that's a, we were in the car chase.
I think that was, I thought it was a black car,
but the only thing we found him,
the clown made him do it.
Clown.
I love his face though, he's always like,
he's like, oh my God, I had to drive around Arthur all day.
Hey, thinkin' that is, do you wanna go to a wrestling match?
I'm a Mexican wrestler, that's what we're going to do.
I know Arthur, no.
Aren't there I don't want to go anywhere. I don't want it. I don't feel like it Arthur. I I don't want to
Thing it is you're not pretty much fun. I know I'm just a normal guy
I'm just a normal bald guy and you're a clown and yeah, I mean you're in here and look at your outfit
I know who thing it is. Do you want to get me out of these clothes? Oh
You're like another massage. I don't know. I don't know what I don't think I want to do. I don't want to
Why you don't want to do anything sounds like burden Ernie kind of a little bit John Gacy
Yeah, I think why are you doing driving John Wayne Gacy around? I didn't know Arthur was still killed John Wayne Gacy and like
imagine that
My interview is a really I don't know. I swear. I didn't do that. Like I'm really like this bass
I like I like bringing you out like I can understand I need to like
Sing of some more because I like almost a lot of I had to type it like I had to kick I had to kick
One of the characters out of the car I forgot I think the ghost or something
It was like oh, this is too offensive. This is not a lot by the safety field filter
Yeah, well, he's supposed to be but yeah, he's not even driving. He's in the passenger seat driving
Look at the clown is like, I'm not gonna. I'm not gonna. He's driving on the freeway
He's like you're going a hundred miles an hour there. He's very concerned
See how calm he is though. Hi. Oh, I can drive a hundred mile an hour car. Hey, I'm a real man
That clown that clown really changed his life, you know
That's who thing is and I hope him and Bita are happy forever. Oh, yeah
Oh my god, I'm so silly
It's Pogo the clown
That was um, I'm sorry. I love I don't want to
You're the passenger see that's thing that is yeah, you're the passenger seat, but you're driving
He's on driving. Did you see him? I see that's your hand on the wheel
Look, you can see the guys at the suit his arm is on the wheel and then the clown is not touching the wheel at all
It's like standing up on the seat. Look how calm you are though. That's pretty cool
That yeah, that's the retarded woman in clown and a clown makeup. It's not worth there. If we'll do again
But no, what is the retarded woman? Oh, yeah, did you other than date?
Didn't you like hang up that didn't you like leave the show when I asked you that when I asked if you would like to
Be dating a well cuz I think I could arrange that I
Said
You went in date no, well, and you said hell. No get it. No. Hell. No. Okay. I don't
You just turn that around trunk full of lime
Yeah, what kind of are what kind of drugs are you okay? So you need to think of another one on let me see I
Mean I can do like I can do this all night. I actually like I can think of funny things. Let me see
Let me see if I can figure out some more.
I just said, I think Conan O'Brien did a skit before
or like a thing where it was like,
he did all these things, but there are all these pictures
and he's like, we went to the sleeper,
there's all these pictures of this thing
and then they're doing terrible things
and it's all, I want to think, be funny like that.
I don't know.
But yeah, like, you know, just having this,
it's like completely stealing the entire thing.
Okay, hold on.
So I think.
This is like magic guys. This is like how I work kind of magic. It's like
Performing for you guys
This is like this is like my version of PM I hit these keys, but the funny part in that music comes after
Don't know maybe you're laughing people. I it's it's regenerating it. Okay. Oh my gosh. This is a great one, too
Guys, this now it's gonna be like, you know guys
I think I do believe in romance again because I was saying I almost don't believe in romance
I think I'm starting to believe in love again. Yeah
There it is
Look at three shining moons, but there's three moons now. It's actually the same that isn't in the ball cloud and
It's pretty beautiful look at the look at the nose smashing against the face. It's like you take off
the you should take out the nose. I mean, I mean
It is what are you what are you doing with this clown?
That is that a female clown is that the retarded woman or is that a is there another person?
I'm not rich. I mean, it's I don't know. I don't want to I know it's not Noel
Well, it might be I don't know. Is it you don't like clowns?
But but you fell in love with one, right? Because it looks like I
Mean I have an album full of photos of you this clown
And there you are making out and you said you didn't remember I call you making with the mannequin too
And the thing that is is like, you know, you can't know I need to think of another one now
Hold on. Okay. Hold on. It's like so hard. You have to get it right. My ideas always
are like, oh, let's filter probably get that. Well, let's see. Okay. Let me see it. Maybe
Okay, well, I think I have another winner. I do. Oh my god. This is a good one
I didn't get I think you guys I just want you guys to the spinal
But I'm thinking is can you tell me who in the fuck is this?
You like my thumbnail I you're hitting you're hitting
That was so mean. Yeah, what is this thing it is? How did we get into it? What is this? You don't like clowns
This is like the fifth clown. I have a view
What are you watching there porn?
Why why do you have pennywise over your smoke are you smoking you're smoking I thought you quit
That you quit that clown bring you smokes
You know, it's always a devil that comes in you think it's gonna come on like scary. It comes in
It comes in something don't make you laugh and so
smile
Yeah
Why is it why is every who is it are these are these men or women because sometimes you can't tell but it's like
You know, they were like
You're smoking in bed memory close ever when you quit and then remember when you started really being relaxed again
And we're like are you smoking and then you were like I was an outside all the time. Oh, yeah
I'm just outside to get some air. We hear like
Can I hide your main? I don't think you're hidden
Yeah, yeah, if you promise not to copyright strike me for using your thumbnail
hold on I
Mean, I don't know. I mean it's hard to realize that it's like
People can, people could like, really, I don't like,
okay, hold on, I'm trying to do right now,
see, you're not mad at me, hold on.
God, you got me in a good mood tonight.
Okay, so let me see who's hidden.
I'll tell you who's hidden right now.
Nobody.
There's no, not one person is hidden.
Nobody's hidden.
Hold on, no, this is the wrong channel, hold on.
No, no, yeah, yeah, yeah, this is the wrong channel.
Nobody's hidden in the other channel, hold on.
If you go to this channel, switch count.
Okay, okay, let's see
Okay, um
Settings I'll read I'll read who's hidden community moderation
And okay, so it says hidden
Um cloud zack
Hold on. Oh, there's a lot of people. Oh, there's big clips right there big clips. Okay. I'll take you off
Well, Sam man, who fucks Sam? I got blocked. Okay
Anybody else I'm gonna take off of that list
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Okay. This person's here. Okay. Nope. Um, let me see
Okay, perfect.
Okay, so what else should I do more?
I mean, it's like, I think this is like,
I think somebody's got to steal the clown away.
I just think we need to do another character.
Okay, but it's like, then it's hard.
I can't describe some of the people.
Hold on.
Okay, hold on.
I'm gonna try a couple of things.
Let me see if I can do this one.
Let's see if we'll do this.
It's another recreated, but it will, like,
don't even care, really, but it just doesn't want you
to do, like, something hardcore.
But I think, oh, I did it.
Guess, guys, because you can guess who all these people are,
You'll just have to tell me.
And this is kind of like, this is what I call,
is it walking away or walking towards, OK?
You like that one?
That's Mason there
And that maybe it means a choice between Mason or
Whoever's in that clown outfit
You're repressing I think it's Arthur it's Arthur you're repressing I think art
I think the clown is Arthur we decided I think it was Arthur
but then it's like I think we can take turns we're in the clown outfit and
Whoever it's just like part of the being an occult
Yeah, that's Sam and it's like this is Sam in his normal appearance
He actually was born with a rainbow wig and juggling balls
Yeah, where's Mason Mason hates me now because I was like, I was like, oh Mason
I was like because thing that thing that isn't I pretend we didn't know him and
He was new. Yeah, it's so mad that we're trying to fool him. I'm never talking to you again
You guys are bullying me. I was like, oh my gosh. I think it is we're bullying him
Then he left and I've seen a sense. He's so mad
But always that we were just pretending that we didn't know who he was. We're like, oh, yeah. Oh, that's um. Oh, he's new
I mean, were you here last time? I have no I've never seen him before. He got so mad
He's on grinder or someone called him up for grinder. He is well
Baclips, you know, he said he asked me if I wanted to be his girlfriend. I
Mean what I mean really do I made that even?
That he'll have to tell myself. I'm actually a woman in order to date me. I mean, I don't know
The mental hula hoops you have to shake my shake to get through life. I don't know
He still is you I know good grief. I know
He asked me how I want to be his girlfriend the loser
I want to be your girlfriend. Yeah, how can I be your girlfriend? And I'll wear I'll wear like a burqa and stuff
And I'll just I'll just obey you. I'll just worship you
I'll do everything you want
He's not a clown. I know. Well, like he said bae let's
Like some batshit crazy. Yeah
Bae I mean, I don't want to see bae is too crazy. I want I need someone like more crazy less crazy than me
Because then if it's like we're too crazy people who know what would happen. I need someone sane to
Pull me out of the
Pit I'm not not somebody I can you know, go swim in you know river sticks with
Is my taint shaved who you're talking to you're asking the kind of question you're sick
The last thing that is things like that. He doesn't answer. Yes, his body is waxed. He's no hair on his body
Not one hair
I think he was asking you you don't look like you have hair there. See you
What is this? What alley is this? Why is there a drum set set up? Where are you? What are you doing?
Here's the thing is we have the photos
What he was just like
Why was there a clown like did someone hire him or did you get him for free?
What's going on here? Just someone explain it to me. I just don't get it. I don't get it
It's a great alley
Thing that is don't try to be funny
disgusting okay let me see what else they have hey leave the comedy to leave the
comedy to like you know me no I'm not really fine
what do I have? I'm just a little bit like her flimped her perclimbed her
Yeah, I have this story here. Let's watch this story.
Ver, a quantum scary tale.
They say Iraq was the greatest weaver who ever lived.
Not in the way poets did it, but in a way that made people stop walking.
Made them stand at her door and forget to breathe.
She didn't just weave cloth.
She wove truth.
Scenes so real that the gods themselves had been spotted peering from the sky, trying to catch a glimpse.
That should have been the warning.
When gods looked down that way, not with fondness, but with attention, something is already ending.
She was young from Lydia.
Her father died willful living, staining his hands purple-black every day.
Iraq watched those hands, the way dice spread through fibers like a secret spreading through
a crowd.
She learned to see structure, the thing beneath the thing.
By the time she was a woman, nobles brought her linen.
Priests brought her ceremonial cloth.
Someone whispered her gift must have come from Athena, goddess of craft and wisdom.
Iraq laughed.
I taught myself, she said.
Even, it was the laugh that did it.
The old woman appeared the next morning, gray shawl bent.
Spine, eyes the color of a winter sky.
She came with a smile that was almost kind and sad.
Child, reconsider your words.
Athena is generous to those who honor her.
Apologize.
She may forgive you.
I'll say it to her face, or act sad.
If she wants a contest, I'll give her one.
I'm not afraid of gods.
The old woman's eyes changed.
Not shifted, changed.
Like a mask dropped straight through the floor.
And Athena stood there, grey eyes now electric, armor catching light that came from nowhere.
Then we weave, she said.
They set up their looms in the open square.
The whole village came.
When a god and a mortal sit down, you don't stay home.
Athena wove the gods in all their glory.
Zeus on his throne.
Poseidon raising seas.
Apollo with his light.
The God's triumphant, righteous, beautiful.
In each corner, a mortal who had challenged heaven, punished, each one ruined.
A woman turned to a crade, a man turned to stone.
The images so vivid they seemed to breathe.
It was a masterpiece.
It was also a threat.
And then...
They looked at Ragn's work.
The crowd went silent, not because it was bad.
Because it was devastating, Ragn had woven the gods too, but not in glory.
She wove Zeus in disguise, seducing mortal women who didn't know what they were agreeing
to.
She wove Apollo abandoning those who loved him.
She wove Poseidon's cruelty dressed as power.
Every scene technically perfect.
Watching carefully for years, the cloth didn't just show the stories.
It showed the pattern, what the gods were, underneath.
You could not look at it and unsee it.
Athena stared at Iraq's tapestry for a long time.
The crowd held its breath.
Here is the part the myths leave out.
Athena was not angry because...
Ragn lost, not even because Ragn won.
Athena was angry because the cloth was true truth once woven into the world.
Is a different kind of power, a power that anyone can hold and carry and show to others.
That is the power that lasts.
She struck the loom first, then Ragn ran, or tried to, the transformation was faster.
Then running, a slow, horrible folding inward. Her fingers lengthening, her spine curving,
her vision fracturing into eight directions at once. The last human thought she had, some
accounts say, was clarity. Not terror. Not regret. Just a cold, complete understanding
of what she had done and why, and what it had cost, and that she would do it again.
And then she was small, and dark, and ate legs, and she began to spin.
Here is what they don't tell you in school.
The spider never stopped leaving the same tapestry.
In every web, if you look close enough, if you know what you're seeing, the same scenes
are there.
Gods in disguise.
Power and its hungers.
The gap between the story they tell and the story that is actually true.
Every morning, Gulet, hanging in corners and doorways and the dark spaces between things.
A reminder, a record, an act of witness that has outlasted every temple built to Athena.
She is still weaving, she never stopped.
Sweet dreams, Saki.
Sleeping beauty.
Hmm
Sorry, I always take things too far
I've seen an image so shocking, so utterly paradoxical, that it stopped you in your tracks.
Today we're rediving deep into the world of one of the most enigmatic and visually stunning figures
in the Hindu pantheon, the goddess Chinnamasta. Her name literally means she whose head is
severed, and her imagery is one of the most powerful paradoxes you'll ever encounter.
So, grab a seat, open your mind, and let's unravel the profound mysteries of the self-decapitating goddess.
At first glance, Chinnamasta is terrifying. You see a goddess?
standing bold and powerful, holding her own severed head in one hand. From her neck,
three jets of blood spurred forth. One stream arcs into the mouth of her own severed head,
while the other two nourish her two devoted attendants, Dikini and Varnini, who stand on either
side. It's an image of what seems to be ultimate self-destruction, a graphic scene that can be
deeply unsettling. But this is where the first paradox lies. Is this an act of violence? Or
something else entirely? To understand Shinna Masta, we need to look beyond the initial shock.
She is often depicted standing on top of Kama, the God of Desire, and his consort Rati,
who are in an intimate embrace. This isn't a random detail, it's a powerful symbol.
By standing on the embodiment of worldly desire and carnal attachment,
Chinamasta demonstrates her complete mastery over these forces.
She isn't destroying herself. She is transcending the limitations of the physical ego.
This brings us to the core of her teaching, the paradox of life, death, and nourishment.
The act of severing her own head is not suicide.
It is a profound voluntary sacrifice. The head represents the ego, the mind, the endless chatter
of thoughts, attachments, and worldly identities that often hold us back. By cutting it off,
Chinamasta performs the ultimate act of spiritual liberation. She detaches from the limit itself
to reveal the boundless, universal consciousness that lies beneath. And what happens after this
death of the ego? Life flows. Her blood, the very essence of life, doesn't spill wasted on the ground.
It becomes a source of nourishment.
She feeds her own severed head, symbolizing that even in a state of enlightenment,
the mind must be sustained with life force.
But more importantly, she nourishes her devotees.
This is the ultimate act of compassion.
She gives her own lifeblood to sustain others.
This transforms the image from one of self-destruction
to one of radical, selfless giving.
She is both the consumer and the consumed,
the giver of life and the life that is given.
This is the great cycle of creation and destruction.
all embodied in one single dynamic image.
Life feeds on life.
For something new to be born, something old must pass away.
We see this in nature all the time.
A seed must break open a sprout, a star must collapse to create new elements.
Chinamasta is the cosmic embodiment of this perpetual cycle.
She is the life giver, the life taker, and the life sustainer, all at once.
She teaches that death is not an end, but a transformation unnecessary
part of the continuous flow of universal energy.
Another fascinating paradox is her connection to both spiritual liberation and raw, untamed power.
Chinmasta is one of the Mahavidyas, the ten great wisdom goddesses.
Each represents a different facet of the Divine Feminine and a path to enlightenment.
Chinmasta's path is direct, radical, and requires immense courage.
She represents the Kundalini energy, the coiled serpent power that lies dormant at the base of the spine.
When awakened, this energy rushes up through the central channel.
Blast in through the chakras and culminating in enlightenment at the crown.
The three jets of blood from her neck are often interpreted as representing the three main psychic
channels. Or nadis. The idea, the pingala, and the central sushamna. Her self-decapitation symbolizes
the moment the kundalini energy bursts through the final knot at the throat or third eye,
resulting in the explosion of consciousness and the dissolution of the ego. So,
while her image is one of control and transcendence over desire, she is also the embodiment of that
powerful, and sometimes frightening life force.
She is the controlled explosion, the disciplined release of immense spiritual power.
She teaches that true power doesn't come from suppressing our vital energy,
but from understanding, mastering, and directing it towards a higher purpose.
Think about the courage it takes to confront the things that define us, our thoughts,
our identity, our ego and be willing to let them go for the sake of something greater?
This is the challenge China Master presents. She asks us.
Are you brave enough to sacrifice your limited self to discover your unlimited nature?
Are you willing to give of yourself so completely that your own life force can nourish the world
around you? Her symbolism is a direct confrontation to our fear of death and our attachment to the
ego. In our modern world, we often do everything we can to avoid confronting mortality. We build
up our egos, our identities, our personal brands, Chinamasta slices right through all of that.
but in being able to offer it up.
The nourishment she provides her attendance as a reminder that spiritual awakening isn't
a selfish pursuit.
The goal of enlightenment is not just to liberate oneself, but to become a source of life and
sustenance for all beings.
The liberated individual becomes a fountain of compassion and energy for the world.
So, the next time you see the startling image of Chinamasta, try to look past the initial
shock.
See the courage, the compassion, and the profound wisdom.
there is the greatest expression of life. In the severing of the self, there is the discovery of
the true self, and in this terrifying image, there is a beautiful and powerful message of
liberation, selfless giving, and the endless, vibrant cycle of the cosmos. She is a reminder
that sometimes, the most profound truths are hidden within the greatest paradoxes. Thank you
so much for joining me on the steep dive into the mysteries of Shint Namasta. If this exploration
Where is it like one of them on stage?
What big lips you never join a show you look like you're you look like you were just working Nickelodeon
I'm probably were investigated by the FBI. I mean, it's like
That's it. I'm sorry
Thing that is looks like he should be on you know a watch list
Yeah, I mean everyone has their problem here like you know
Some people are maybe government agents. Some people probably probably government informants people probably anarchists
I mean it's like it's a big mix
I must stay okay. Yeah, okay. Well, I'm gonna say to you
Not not must a hey mama stay. I don't know
You look like the transformer
Transporter. Oh right there. I
Know we had fun doing this
Like then we have we didn't we have fun doing some of these images like we're taking this photo shoot earlier thing
That is remember this photo shoot we took
It's you in bed with and then look
It's some good good images
So this is the you know, you had a great trip, you know, oh, yeah, there you are
When did you go to hell with it?
Oh, that's when you went and met Gotti for it over a minute. What's up easy?
Mason looks more like good times in the picture.
Well, no, Mason's in this picture over here.
Remember when Mason was there?
I don't know about that.
He's right there in the alley, see?
Hi, Gunny.
Mason.
Hey, Gunny!
Remember when you were in the convertible?
Did you win it at the dealership because or it's like what is it like a Corvette these are those balloons
You get for winning it and then you let the clown hold and why are you driving when you're the passengers? I don't know
There's you on them as ex-inquadra Maya earlier this month
And like you've never been happier though in your life. Have you like look at that glow?
You didn't all you needed was a guy to like you're gonna like hold your hand stuff, right?
You're gonna nice little massage too
Remember how surprised you were that first night. You didn't think you'd enjoy gay sex that much did you? Oh
Oh is Jamie, I don't know
Jamie can address that if she wants to I mean she has her last name. Oh, no, no, she doesn't know she doesn't
I
Think she must not be dating
Jesus thong it is
Dang, no one wants to smell your thing. Oh, I
Please undan Damian day. Why would I abandon Damian day?
Should I look in my message history and see why that person was blocked?
Or just don't make me waste my time if I'm gonna look down and we shot how terrible it was whatever they said
Is Damien's it what I suppose I can give Damien to another chance if you ask me nice next time
It'll be okay Damien's unhidden, but next time I'd like you to send me $5 if you're gonna ask me in the middle
So you're gonna my mods are banning
mass unban
Send me some send me some cash. I'll do a massive ban if I make $20 and it's cash ups
I thought my things on the screen
I do appreciate anybody helping me out.
Oh my gosh, it's already, it's 12 o'clock,
I need to make sure I need to cancel this
in one second, I'll be right back.
Shit.
Let me see.
Oh, shit.
I don't know.
I mean, I was able to do it last time.
Billy, a car.
I had no one's band probably.
I just needed to cancel it before I get it,
but I don't know how I did it last time.
I just like, I pushed something last time
and I just ended up on the page.
Oh, hold on.
General Billy, hold on.
That might have been it.
Car, car, they've been failed.
Okay, good.
Good, good, good.
Okay, thank God.
Oh no, oh no, it keeps trying to charge it.
And I'll take it, I mean, they can do that,
but then I'm gonna take a few days.
Okay, hold on.
No billing. No, okay. Oh wait, but according to the okay managed plan. I can cancel from here cancel. Thank God found it
Okay, cancel downgrade pan. Oh, I'm just gonna cancel the
Cancel the benefits
Okay, I
Did it I did it the stream turn off. Let me see if I have any more clips. Oh, it says more clips are generated. Let me see
Watch clips on streamer. I don't know. I'll look into it. No, no, no one should be banned
Are you the streamer? Okay here
Stretch out, feel the sunshine glow.
Um, thank you for your one.
That's, all this, as you can see, it's working, okay?
I mean, you can see what I said.
All I said is, what happened last night?
What happened to this?
Oh my god, who is that?
Help me.
I don't know why I'm wearing the wig.
I don't know some of the stuff.
I don't know everything, but here's sir in the alley. Oh my god. I'm trying my friend
She's in a calendar. I'm gonna what I'm gonna help in the bathroom. It's like a oh my god
I'll put up. I'll try put on a video or some grip. There's sir in that art gallery
Have to my other clothes bro, I don't care to get a haircut
Oh, I don't feel I don't feel like getting a haircut. I
Also don't feel like giving myself a haircut and that's why do you want to see what it looks like without the beanie?
It's a disaster
I have too much hair
I got too much hair and I'm like a lot of that's the thing
The thing the thing is that I have hair and I'm balding at the same time. It's a good
It's actually a good psyche. Shut the fuck up psyche. I was speaking
$200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $200 $
I
Dog HQ, I wonder what a psychological evaluation of yourself would reveal. I wonder
This is something this is something that I've said
I've said this countless times. I'll say it again
All of the these chatters they like to criticize the streamers and they have so much to say about the streamers
Like they're these abhorrent people. They're doing this is doing that. I
Would be really interested in seeing right these chatters
These chatters. Let's see what your actual life is like. Let's see what your psychological evaluation
Because I think I have a feeling that
The chatter is a psychological evaluation on average is going to be worse than streamers
There you're yapping as well more or less
But yeah, shout out to you
Towards you buddy. I wish you the best that being said that being said
No, let me talk to this. Let me talk to this. We'll find that she left her
BBO
No, you can't talk to me. I'm I'm spoken for
By whom?
By JT
Fuck him
JT what just thinking you just thinking about JT. What is JT standing for?
It's definitely true mom. I've been doing fentanyl. What's up?
What about it?
And what about I do fentanyl?
Maybe we can change
That does fentanyl. So what?
Now, let me speak to her. Yeah, fuck JT. Yeah
JT you want to come up here? Hey speak your claim
He's on vacation weirdo. Hey mom, they can't he doesn't exist
Exits
Shout out to a racer rain. She's watching my stream
W. Yeah, I am watching your stream W
Well W
That's not a W. You got these hot ass Mexican bitches on my stream. What are you doing?
Let me ask you a question. Who the fuck is JT?
My boyfriend
This fucking retard he fucking bit I was asking you a question, but oh yeah, all right
Don't call Sega retard
He doesn't pay attention to sure
Not see there we go. He thinks it's the something
Now just my boy does Wesley know who JT is
Yeah, he does
Have ever debated JT him and JT go way back
What year was it
Oh, I'm nineteen ninety-four or something. Yeah, that makes sense, that's all right, that makes sense.
No, listen, if you want me, JT's never going to hear this, you can be honest right now.
What do you mean?
Oh my, Annie played the fucking game.
Did I play volume? What's that guys? I can't hear anyone.
I think there's something I think you racist that there's something going on with
the stream art or some shit
What?
No, you said that we couldn't like when you first joined you can hear it. I know oh
Yeah, apparently it's like an iPhone thing. I don't know. That's what our G said
That's why you should go with Android
Fuck Android
That's her broke bitches
Right a VW
Okay, she took time out of her day from playing golf just to talk to us
W I'll take one with you brother. I'll take one with you
I don't know. I want a Dr. Pepper.
I think nothing wrong with the Dr. Pepper. Ain't nothing wrong with that.
Do you like it cold or lukewarm?
Cold.
Well, all right. There's no debate here. I can see it. She wants.
No.
All page left. No.
Well, she said her shit was she said her stuff was messing up. She'll probably rejoin
W
And now I can't hear anybody
Can't hear me don't be a scissor
W
Yeah, I'll say you're gonna have to come back because they're all gonna leave because nobody cares about me. Imagine me up here
I'm back
Where the hell
Hey, fuck you psych. Hey, fuck you dog
We're all the regulars
Um, it's, uh, it's Thursday night. Um, I don't fucking know.
No, you raised her. Did that, that image that just came up, do you like that a little bit?
It looks a little bit better than JT, correct?
What came up?
Sorry, show her again.
She needs to be seen. She has permission to crush out.
Oh, I crashed out early. I'm fine. Oh, was it a good crash out? Yeah, it was
Oh, you like that or what?
What the hell is that fat fuck?
What'd you just say?
Yeah, who the hell is that? No, but you know you don't say who the hell was that what do you say?
I said who the hell is that?
Now you said fat fuck dude clean your ears. I did not say that shit. Well, bitch talk correctly. Yeah
Don't call me a bitch bitch
No, I'm sorry. I meant to call you princess my bad. I'm sorry. I misspeak sometimes my bad. Yeah, exactly
Don't call me a black guy. I meant to call you beautiful. I'm on you
Do you say
Never mind. I don't say anything. Don't actually don't ask me. Why are you trying to guess like him?
You not saying I'm not trying to guess like anybody. I my knee. I'm fucking hurt right now
Does anybody care about me being hurt?
Would you do I fell for you
Lame
Oh, better than JT, though.
Lane Pickup Line.
Better than JT, though.
Let me give you, if I had the like,
you'd be like, hey, can you win me over ghost?
How would you do it?
Let me, I'll give you one word right now.
You want to know what I, like, literally,
let everybody clip it and ship it.
It would be money.
Dude, you're weird.
How much that was this, you know, let's even have to explore that. How am I weird? That was very disrespectful
Kind of hurtful actually. I wouldn't call you like you would never call you you called me a bitch
So that was pretty hurtful. Yeah, that's cuz that's I call no, that's like saying female
I didn't mean it and no disrespect. You know that but you I don't like to be called that shit anyways
Well, you could have said ghosts. I don't like to be called that please
And I never I didn't say that you can after that
Okay, good God her one that one
Listen, man, I'm gonna win that heart. I'm gonna win your heart
No, yeah, yeah
I'm gonna I'm gonna win that heart because you keep making these dumb dumb arguments and like listen I
Got much
I don't date white guys. I date Mexican guys good day. I'm black
The only dates white guys that are Mexican
JT is half way and he's half Mexican so he's still Mexican. He's also half fucking retarded. We all have our own crosses to bear whatever
But what I'm saying is that you got your big buddy like, you know
No, I
Once you cut your boyfriend to come up here and defend your ass
I don't need anybody to defend me. I could defend myself.
You need to defend yourself?
Yeah.
Yeah, you made a lot of mistakes.
You don't want to fucking mess with a feisty Latina bitch.
No, I do want to fuck with them.
That's like my main priority. I like to fuck them.
I mean, what the fuck?
I kind of recommend you don't.
Why not?
Because I'll fucking drag your shit.
Oh shit! What the fuck? I was talking about them, not you! Shit!
Oh, okay. Well, never mind then.
Damn! Girl, you're crashing up for no reason. You're crashing up. You have permission to crash out. Go ahead, crash out.
I already told you. I did that earlier.
And by the way, you're the first female I ever gave permission to crash out. Go ahead, crash out. Do your thing.
I did that earlier, I never listen, you never listen.
I'm listening now.
Good.
That's something I'm bad at.
I also never listen.
Be a good girl.
Yes.
No, but this guy over here is just, I don't know.
We'll crash out.
If you want to crash out, crash out.
Go ahead.
Fuck, I'll crash out with you.
That's those locals
Leslie dub you
You're not gonna say dub you I'm not gonna do it on the shop
Fuck is that guy
Yeah, okay, we'll do
Now, let me talk to a mamacita or whatever your name is. What's your name?
Mamacita? No, it's rain. Sorry, sorry.
It's rain.
Maybe my future.
Maybe beautiful.
Maybe,
Mi niña bonita, mi doce princesa.
Acaya amor?
Okay.
I don't understand your accent.
Mi niña bonita, mi doce precesa.
You can Google it if you want.
I mean, if you're really that hard.
You're not even fucking Spanish.
I'm not going to. Do I have to repeat this?
You should have given me this.
You're not fucking Spanish.
You don't understand the fucking.
You don't want to. Yes, but no.
You must be in the home?
Mi niña.
Bonita.
Mi doce.
Princesa.
No money.
You fucking fake, you fucking you're probably about, you probably, I don't know if you're
having a melt, but you ain't fucking Spanish, I know that, you hear?
You don't lost your chance with that.
That was very simple.
This bitch is that she kind of stupid. You don't know SIG SIG translate for him
Yeah
You don't know what anything means bitch, I don't know what that means
Go ahead. I'll translate for rain when that means fuck yourself
Thank you, sir. Exactly means go fuck yourself. I mean that makes sense
No, what's your little bitch JT up here here? Yeah, it means more like suck my dick
You see
Go ahead and Google that shit. Yeah, I mean you know bonita me don't say princess. Oh, yeah
She wants you know what she wants me I
Don't want you though. I'm not some kind of piece of me. All right. I know you want me
But I'm gonna have to let you down slowly here
No, it's not
I want to be a baller, but listen, it's not you, it's me.
I just hurt my heart.
Actually, it was me.
I have to lay down slowly here, girl.
Listen, you're a very beautiful girl.
You're a very beautiful girl, but I'm just not feeling it.
Fill all the killers in the hundred dollar bill is
We ain't got no feelings now listen now listen you you flirt with me. I
Get his content, but listen. I'll have to let you down slowly. I need some kind of peace for me. All right
Are you still talking to yourself
Yeah, chat or you if you're listening baby chat
Are you a predator?
The fuck maybe you're maybe JT is a predator
No, it sounds like JT stands for just trying
Sounds like you're projecting kids
Is that what you mean?
Onto somebody that's not even here
Hey, fuck you her and them you really?
Beautiful man right there, but remember
That's me looks like me sounds like me. Why are you ball?
Old age
Why are you a whore?
How am I a whore?
How are you actually the question do you see me hitting on any other men? No weirdo
I guess JT just trying
Don't laugh don't laugh don't fucking laugh. Hey yo
All right, it's like I've been waiting it's it's early, but can I permission?
It's not gives me the mission. I'm gonna burn you and your little fucking retard friend up here up
Why are you trying to talk shit on sick
Cuz he's fucking retard it. I mean, what the fuck well, can I have permission if not, let's just
Did you just give me the mission to
Yes!
Oh yeah, fucking hell.
Hey listen, you stupid ass fucking whore.
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
You don't know who the fuck you're talking about.
You don't know who the fuck you're talking to.
You're stupid.
You don't know-
He's following you on board.
You join.
Well listen, bitch.
You want backup from SIG?
That's a good-
Oh yeah, let me help.
Maybe ask for someone a little bit more smarter than SIG.
SIG's fucking stupid.
Because I know you're not talking to me.
I'm talking to you, bitch.
Start it up.
I'm talking to you.
You had a problem with that you do have a problem with that explain yourself. Why do you have a problem with it?
I'm giving you the chance go ahead
What do you have a problem, you know, I fucking save you because your tube returned to have the conversation
What made you so upset that I called you ugly that I called you retarded or that called you stupid?
What do you have a problem with?
Your shit doesn't work on me
You can't rage rate me what the fuck I'm not trying to rage rate you what do you have a problem with you?
They're probably anything
Okay
We should deport your shit guys guys like guys
This bitch
You have a problem. You know you have a problem. Why are you being fake just say you have a problem with something
And we'll talk about it. You know, we don't have to debate or argue. We can talk
Now you're you're thinking thinking thinking just fucking talk stop thinking good. Oh, yeah
Hey, yo psych this bitch is even more retarded than fucking I'll I'll say it even more retarded that signal
I have to put that out there
But you're stupid, though
You can at least made it like you could at least learn about being funny. You're too stupid. You don't know what the fuck you're talking about
What's this idiot rage about me?
I'm having a bad dream, but my pain is going to help.
Oh, fuck you, sir!
I'm having a bad dream.
Am I just gonna start with E and then with R?
Is this a real life? Is this just fantasy?
You know, Syke, Syke, Syke, why you're up here, why you're still listening. Do you know who's Outer Ring? What's your running?
Do you know her? We're going on YouTube.
It goes like this.
Rain falls upon my windowsill.
Oh, yeah.
It's raining.
Rain drops keep falling on my wings.
I just familiar with the song because my child is at a song ranch.
Oh.
She is stupid as my boy Wesley up here.
Yeah.
Oh, that's stupid.
She's more smarter.
She's more smart.
Oh, you think she's more smarter?
More smarter than him.
More smarter than the average bear.
Yeah, she's smart. She's smart.
Don't fuck with Rage.
Let's go.
You know she wants unless she want to says one unless you want to say one nice thing about me
We say one nice thing about each other and go in a circle. I think we should go around the circle. Yeah, okay
Oh, we have another guest coming
You start I bring the new guests on though. We have a new guest a welcome. I want to welcome
Say one new birth a one nice thing
Okay, one nice thing what we said, but I want to show somebody have to like scroll down a little bit. Can I call him up?
Let's welcome beautiful from the Dolphin City of the World
Hi Paige. Hi, how's it going Rain?
I was saying hi to Paige rude. Yeah, cool. We were all saying hi at the same time
Well, you gotta wait
What do you guys do about that page that's okay, don't worry about it
Yeah
It's good I got to golf today like in my yard and read my field I guess you could say so I'm sad to win for me
But I'm nice. I know you're passionate about going. I
Think Paige would like this what we were just talking about is everyone goes around the circle and says something one thing nice about each other page
We're actually she's a positive person. She loves that kind of stuff that I can condone. Yeah, for sure. Yeah, I know you do
I have one before we go. I have one question. How did you what did you do with the golfing? How'd you do?
Really good actually. There was one try
Still really good, but not
But to gauge it, I guess I would have been about maybe like 230 yards and then 250 yards
Yeah, I mean I ain't gonna argue with that. That's not bad for a couple of my first nine and argue with that
Not a bit here
Page can I ask you a question a personal question if you don't mind. Thanks. Thank you for wearing that low-cut shirt
You look wonderful
Page how do you keep how do you you look like I like looking at you listen
How do you keep it me so beautiful all the time like any time I see you you're always positive and beautiful
That's just because that's how I am. That's just how I am ghost. I appreciate your compliments. Thank you
You're welcome Wesley.
Positive to use the choice and beauty is in the eye of the beholder, so thank you.
You're very welcome.
Yeah, let's see this one here.
I'm here.
I just finished my drink.
I had to step away from it.
But yeah, how you been?
Good, um, I mean like obviously, I know everybody's been kind of going through their own shit in their own way
But like good for good for life and still breathing and blinking. We're okay
But we all understand we all understand you're like you're beautiful. We all understand that we all agree
But how do you say so positive?
Honestly
You haven't really earned a reason for me to not be positive to you yet cuz I mean like it's a choice like I said
Just because my shit the if I'm having a bad day or whatever just don't bleed on those who didn't cut you kind of thing
You know what I mean? I know you've ever done anything
Pretty easy to be I'm gonna go ahead and agree with her. She doesn't come from the debate world. She doesn't know anything about that. Like
Argue with each other and shit
Don't let her fool you though
I will debate you all day long. I just don't want to ruin my head.
You're such an instill dude.
I need a beer.
I mean I agree with that.
Now, Saik, what the fuck happened to your t-shirt bro?
Oh, my lighter.
Saik.
Is that a cut off shirt?
It looks like a purple, it looks like a purple white beater.
That's not butt.
Wow.
We kind of do not show your butt.
That's not your butt.
What kind of beard are you drinking?
Um, usually it's papst, but I don't mind, uh, Coors Banquet and I like Rainier as well.
Not a bad choice.
I'm not gonna pay full price for light beer the fuck
I'm not you want to a different fucking city like you go to these like hot like these different cities like they want
You talking to
Why are you talking to me like that?
All I said was, you put me to a different city.
Because I was talking to people and you keep interrupting weirdo.
Don't talk to her.
Don't talk to me like that, bitch.
Who the fuck are you?
You're being a bitch.
You're interrupting every fucking time.
You literally just, you literally just.
Shut the fuck up.
Don't talk to me.
Okay, don't talk to me.
Shut the fuck up.
You're stupid as bitch, aren't you?
You know, being with some of these people, is it really worth busting in the fucking snow?
Straight up is that bitch you thought it fucking talking to like that
That's not appropriate to say you can call her a bitch
That's fucked up a little bit right like a lot of it
Like I was saying page I'm drinking her personally I prefer more
Thank you, I mean any better, okay
Personally, so what's your flavor? What do you like?
I drink tequila, um, you know, like, Mexican tequila, of course.
Usually if a female tells me she doesn't like, like, most women I know, if they do drink beer, they will do usually, you know, shots or they don't mind a stiff drink.
But then there's the women who don't fucking drink coolers and they don't drink beer and I'm like, bitch, you drink that right out the bottle all night, don't you?
Like, that's how that goes, usually.
Yeah, I'll drink coolers, I'll drink, you know, margaritas. Those are more of my things.
I like them too, Margarita. Yeah, I'm Margarita, I'm down always for that. I like a homemade one though.
Like, put a little spice in there sometimes, like jalapenos, strawberry margaritas. That's good shit.
Or the tahini, like the chili powder.
Yeah, we can have a hard read of some time I think so I'm like hoping in my mind
I have this like set up of an event and like you know a lot of us to talk about it
I'm some of us all getting together somewhere or not where we live
You know what I mean, but wouldn't that be fucking fun and like having it like a whole you know
We could have a setting for it have a theme for it and like you know certain people and I thought it'd be cool
I have like a bunch of them every time I go to give you a reading though. Oh, no, it's usually one card
One card, okay, let me go get the guy that's made hold on I didn't mean to enter me say sorry to freeing for
Interaction, how'd you know would you do it?
Okay, I can't even hear ghosts anyways
You can't hear me
You're just gonna meet yourself. I mean that makes a lot of sense
Okay, so I've made two decks lately and the one is like more straightforward
It's like the April like quick answer one, but anyways, I also have been working on this dare to be free deck
I got one from that. Yeah, absolutely. That's why I went and got it and it's pretty cool
I mean a lot of the time I drives me nuts like I don't usually use my books for decks
And so I said if I want to make a deck where everything's on the card and everything is just conveniently there for
Eating it and the person who is listening. So anyway, I will uh, is this reading?
Can I ask Paige a question before she gives me a rating I mean a card rating
Hey, do you feel like if somebody asked you for that? Do you feel like you're kind of like a like a
Psychiatrist?
Let me explain what I said that for like you give them a reading and
Then they'll ask you why then you have to explain like
Give a fill up that right now
Um, so I'm a spiritual therapist and it comes with a territory. It doesn't bother me. It I expected with the it's expected with the
with the situations and then
the the territory in general
Okay, thank you. I'll be right back. Okay, sorry
You're like captain interrupt your source over there
I didn't mean to ask you that question, but I think that a lot of people, and even like,
I've talked to like, and I'm not saying you're compared to them at all, but I've talked to like
strippers, I'm like, they're literally like therapists, like, like it's so crazy, it's like
When I was a bartender page, by the way, I'm not comparing what you do to strippers
In that context, you know any job, whatever works is like bartending or things like that
Yeah, 100% so it just kind of is like that thing if people are open
I mean if they're comfortable enough to you know open up to you
That says a lot about who are as a person to you.
So you should take that as a compliment
if someone ever does, right?
I think the weekend of this argument
would be like a waitress, you know.
That blank card was a blank card.
Hey, is that my card?
No, that's not supposed to be in here.
But we don't have a card.
I do.
I mean, two came out when I was shuffling.
Can I get two?
Okay, cuz one of them let's go came out before I bet you will
Let's go. Well, that's fate. That's fate. Let me get to
It's so hard with these. I have to get them like actually made for their car
Well, you keep going you keep going bigger and bigger
Bigger cars
If they're just hard because they're like index cards
Okay, so this is great. So we do have the paliser and
So a person perceived almost angelic or subtly like otherworldly someone
You'll slightly be on the human realm and then we have the this is the desidalia, which is
It is the quiet collapse of admiration for someone once revered when disappointment replaces awe and you can see is the flaw that shattered the illusion, not anger, just the stillness of realization, they were never who you thought.
Hmm should I almost page a page? I almost got I almost got the yin and yang
Yeah, no hundred percent like
Like when I made them this deck is like it's super special to me because it is the understanding of the light in the dark because I
promote people to
Accept, you know acknowledge that about themselves always to find some wholeness or like that's a difficult
Paige, can I say a thing? Can I say something new? I know they're gonna clip it. I've never said this before because obviously I'm a orthodox Christian, but
I once in my past life, well in my past, not past life, but in my past, I tried to create a deck. I could never do it because I was so like
Like if I create this and I create that, like if I'm filming, if I'm filming some type of way, I'm gonna put this in there
But let's say a week later, I feel different, you know what I'm saying?
I'm not saying drawing, I'm not saying drawing like you take the cards out, I'm saying drawing like physically drawing.
Yeah, 100%. But that's because our energy is always in motion. It's constantly in flow.
And it's always going to change. If it doesn't, that's where we have a problem.
So if you didn't feel some sort of way and something didn't make you think or question something the next week.
can i make one point though can i make one point page you know you know like you but
let's say i'm drawing a card and i feel sometimes i feel a different way about it like should i keep
the card i mean probably but should i i mean argumentally debatable no i shouldn't keep that
And that's my problem.
If it resonates with you, it's for you.
If it doesn't, leave it, it's not for you,
it's for someone else.
And so that's where the difference is
when I'm doing a personal reading,
read's easier to be more specific,
but when you're doing a reading online
where there's much energies like involved,
a bunch of them.
And so you're gonna pick up on the odd thing
that isn't of the person directly that's asking for that.
I don't really have any.
So much with that I can I can tap in focus like personally for the most part,
but it does get distracting with a lot more energies involved for sure.
I feel like one never like me and Pace obviously would never come to 100%.
Like obviously we've talked we've talked for a while obviously like but I didn't have questions and stuff and like that's why I feel like
But you can even question me about like, you know, like
God and like free will and stuff, but I didn't have questions for you. I had a couple. I did have one more though
Go ahead.
I think, yeah, thank you, Paige.
The one more is like, let's say I'm really filming that way,
and I do make that picture.
I'm going to show it to someone else and say,
that's why you're filming that way.
That's where I get the problem from.
Because I do come from a Christian-based community,
or heritage, whatever you want to say.
But I can't put that on them.
But that's the thing. That's the beauty of like, I mean, yeah
Is that we're all entitled to you, you know our beliefs
Being open-minded enough to either like emulsify them and your own your beliefs as well and taking little things or disagree with them and have like
The greatest thing she's ever did was give us a bottle of fugitive this but let me just personally with my written greatest thing
He ever does he gave us free will
Yeah
That's where the fate things come in ground. Yeah, we did pound it
Yeah, she's a whore
Okay, this is a weird thing. So when it comes to like, you know, I guess
the divine or whatever. If they want interference, they cannot do if you don't give them
the permission to do so because your free will choices will change absolutely your fate 100%
page are you are you are you religious or a spiritual or do you have another word for it or
is it okay that i believe in a little bit of everything and that i don't i think it's okay i'm
gonna judge you yeah so i mean i've i mean i've taken things that resonate or that fit my fit my
my comfort zone or my page if if you were setting up here saying like oh i'm a religious fanatic and
and you didn't claim that I did I would judge you but you've never once made that claim
and you've always been the same ever since I've known you so I don't know if you're spiritual but
you I mean I get what you're doing but I don't think that you're I definitely don't think that
you're a hundred percent religious I'm not trying to be disrespectful when I say that but no you're
not wrong you're not wrong and I'm it's okay to say that I didn't throw up in like a strict religious
And I kind of had a childhood where religion kind of was, we were more worried about surviving than we were worried about like, you know, I mean, like there was practices, obviously, I mean, I've always been, oh, my life's just looking, it's kind of open to everything.
I am open minded to religions. Now listen, this is where I mean, I believe in the creator. That's because of my heritage. That's because of where I come from. So that would be the most.
There has to be, there has to be an ultimate creator.
But there is, that's the thing, a God or everyone's version of God is created from the same higher source or higher power.
It's just, you know, kind of changed or manipulated or worded differently into certain cultures or certain people in power at the time to, I mean, either keep control and or keep them sort of order, if you will.
um but can I no go ahead and I'm sorry go ahead no it's okay but it's all just
based on the same like creator yeah I have to agree with you and let me make it
let me make an argument it gets myself I know it's going to sound dumb
but let me argue against myself because I am religious and I'm
Orthodox Christian but yeah listen if everything's everything has to come
from somewhere so here's the ultimate debate ever
How'd it come from somewhere? So where does it come from?
He I think that that's like the big you can say you can say God
Well, let me read argument again. I'm gonna page for the first time ever
Everybody's gonna clip it. I know this but I'm gonna put my own ass, but it's everything comes from something
Where did he come from? Something had to exist before that
Absolutely, but the thing is, none of us know we have scientific facts.
Okay, I'm very scientific and I'm very much scientific.
I'm very much fax and, you know, I'm a bit of a dreamer too, so.
You might as well obviously you should be, you know, that's smart.
Right, fax and dreaming, both go in the hand and hand, and anyways, long story short, like
tangible facts.
things that have been proven, that kind of thing.
But I also, you know, I'm open to the possibility
of the fact that we don't fucking know everything.
And like, and there was things like that.
And that's, that's-
Paige, we're getting along too long.
Now I gotta, now I think we're gonna have to,
now I gotta disrespect you.
I'm just fucking with you, by the way.
But we usually, it's like, we usually do get along.
I'm not gonna lie like, but I have different,
Obviously I have different like I'm a fucking debater. I never once meant to disrespect you
But obviously I have because I am a debater, but I think we're having a good conversation tonight
I'm pretty open-minded. You haven't really offended me unless you talk like a bitch or some shit. I don't like that
Oh, well, I'm sorry. I was talking about in the past, but no, yeah
Yeah, I think we're having a good conversation
It actually doesn't even bother me when you call me shit like that
Okay, other women shit like that in front of me like I don't like that. That's my biggest
Oh, you're talking about yeah, why can't I can understand that? Oh, yeah
I do say
That bothers me more than you actually insulting me. I'm sorry
Well, it's kind of like what if I said like one plus one was two and then also I said one plus one is a fucking bitch
It's best to I mean
Like I say shit, but like if you actually if you actually listen like sometimes I make sense
But you just heard the bitch part of it, you know
Oh, can I say that word? I'm so sorry. I didn't hear that part
I was actually trying to find some like middle ground of understanding actually
I think we found kind of ground. I think you should keep talking because I really appreciate that and I'm glad we're getting along and
They come from they try to make a second deal
What do you in a team do you put in?
They're those by Alexander Mayer's
We get to say that was a fun birthday right thing that is you love that one. I had a great birthday
You start Star Trek fans out there
I don't know, I mean it's like, do you know, I know a couple, I don't know if you think
that, I think it's like, I was into like more fantasy, kind of fantasy stuff than space
stuff, but I still, I never, I never got, I would, I never got to go to a space camp.
I think I might have gone to Astro Camp one year and it was like cool, they give you like
They think space but it's like how much of like, you know, some of some some of the pool and like
What does it say? Does it say anything under a match in?
Um, I don't know
Um, I can check my screen
I don't know, but I mean she made a few I mean I say I hope that she's a mind like
I think we like, uh, you know, I like I show like, you know
different stuff, but
But I always make sure she gets credit, and you can check out her channels, too.
Actually, I edit her channels, so my regular page is recommended to the channels, so you
can – so, but it's IRL news time.
IP2wiki.info.
I was under mayors.
But, yeah.
We kind of had a meme more, and like, you know, sometimes I was like – but I do have
You know, she's pretty smart and like I like her style and you know, she's a pretty powerful style
So I didn't mean to like kind of like
I could try copy her or anything like that, but I will say she's she was an hour issues the inspiration
and like I think she's pretty
Pretty brilliant. Maybe like ahead of ahead of the time of this world, but you know
Because she's but anyway
Hope she's doing good. I don't know. I've been
Haven't seen here tonight
See anybody other to cat, but did you guys hear cat came back, but it wasn't tricks. It was
his brother
tux
Who is reappeared inside the house after like about almost over a year has been gone
And he just came in and he has like a little white on his chest because I know it's him
And then he's like just sitting and like I thought it was Lenore and I was like oh my god
Yeah, it was like his brother and then I think he already ran out
But I think but I didn't see him go out so he might be inside the house still but
But he but now tricks doesn't chase him out
And so he was like just like sleeping calmly in the cat bed. I was like, oh my god
Like I was like how did he know like like
Tricks wasn't here like are they just like always like go on and say I wonder if the other kid there
I don't like the other cat or something. You know because it's like I'm sure cats can be like that
But I don't think tricks is dead person usually I don't think tricks is dead
I I would have a feeling like I had a feeling when my cat had a cat named silly
He's black and white cat and he got actually got by Coyote, but I just had a bad feeling about other stuff that day
I still don't know. I can tell instantly, but yeah. Yeah. Well, yeah, so I've been hoping maybe tricks would come running in and stuff like that
I love but you know, it's like some like just like I said
This cat like was perfectly the same. They sometimes cats don't like to be in the house with a lot of other cats
I've looked for tricks. Also, there's ads on everything. It won't come me a lazy bum Persian beauty
But this picture is that is that's not my picture is that looks like I saw him been a lot under me
Who is that?
Look for tricks
Yeah, you know, he might be like 37 miles away a more luck finding the actual tricks bunny
At this point, you know, I mean he has to come home. He has like, you know surface your be his brother
He doesn't have a bro. Oh my god. I won't say anything about it
But this is a nice one.
She made this one too.
This is nice.
No, I'm not, you're not gonna pin you.
This is not a, that's another one, Alexander made.
Pretty good.
Because, you know, Q is in a firefighter calendar.
You know that?
Don't want to I don't know who it is
Who do you who are your people? I don't know who some of you are
This is so you see here. There's me with three cats
But
Quietly
LGBTQ
Multiracial impoverished male
What?
Move move in here
Like am I so happy
Look, I finally the good
Well, yeah, I'm like if I get a date with Q
Look how happy I look. I
Think it's a happy ending. I mean, it's I'm really it really is and it's a quietly and like he's doing it
He's with a selfie stick
I thought he said it was a calendar, but he what is he doing? He's holding something
What is that he's holding I
Want to
Hey, I would I would like you know, I would I don't think he's interested in me. I think you would just break my heart
Because I need someone to be in love with me.
I can't be like, oh, and it would be just so weird.
I mean, it's like, what?
Oh, people would say I'm just some kind of perv, you know?
It's like, oh, he likes these smells.
I don't care.
There's not such showers before.
I can go like, oh, let's take a shower, sweetie.
And I'll let me just scrub you real clean.
And then I would get some of that borax or something
like that, I don't know.
Go to town.
Um, he's looking for his what?
What does that mean? Oh, it doesn't sound like it doesn't sound like the right kind. Oh, I like that phrase
Does that mean
Doesn't wear deodorant. Yeah, it's okay
I'll that's what I mean. It's like because one doesn't wear deodorant. It doesn't mean
That they won't put it on when I hand them it and say put this put this on right now
You guys, Benny and the RV, I can't believe that.
You say outrageous things, Persian Beauty.
Are you like, who are you?
I dig the highlights in your hair and that pick.
Yeah, I used to have, I don't know how to say it,
I used to have hair like that.
Like I used to get highlights all the time.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't put it up all.
Like, I just gonna, I mean, I really just want to say
thank you for letting me show those, let me see.
A clips, I can still show the one,
you know, it's like the thumbnail of this video,
but you know,
I mean everyone I just want to say big clips to do this one. It's kind of funny.
I mean I can I have big clips. Can you give me permission to put all these all of your art of
me on just the ones of me on my um on my Colt Codex or or or like you know if you want if you want
like other stuff included you can let me know but I just want to make sure I can use it okay.
Or actually, I can use it for people's,
I'll put it around people's pages too,
if it's okay if I put them freely.
Oh, thank you so much, that's very nice of you.
So maybe, yeah, I just went to jump the gun.
But yeah, I think that'd be kind of funny.
I think they are, I think you are very talented
and it's pretty cool to be able to have like,
actually I've always wanted art done to me
and it's like, you know,
He doesn't give you gay vibes, but you're not gay so your gay art is probably way off
He doesn't but it's like I'd be surprised at like
Masculinity how it works and stuff like that the most masculine people you would meet like are kind of like they have man
They have like man crushes or like, you know the bro crush or whatever or they are kind of commuticulo
kind of things where they realize they can make a like money from gay guys because just by that kind of like
Leading them on a little bit sometimes giving them what they want, but like usually just like, you know
Oh, can I hey daddy? And then like, you know, I don't I don't it's pretending that they're kind of like
I don't know that I mean guys are just kind of scoundrels but women can be scoundrels but guys really are like, you know, it's like
They can just be it because they do like, you know, I can just like
Really
Be scoundrelous beta bones and cure granted date tomorrow. Wow
Thank you, dude. Yeah
Yeah, and it's like yeah, I want some money for money. How are you?
We're just looking at like, you know some art of me, you know looking at
Or really actually the good thing that is
Mexico just good times remember the good times
Alexander Mears. That one.
Who doesn't look like who? Who doesn't look like who? Who? Who?
Chim-chim-chim
Sorry
This is it. It's been a thing. We've got things we've got thing doing this too
You know
It's gonna say a mannequin we thought we saw him gives it it's got it the last second I turn on the camera
So the first picture really didn't look like the thing that the other one did.
Yeah, well, Alexandra fixed it.
Okay, you know, she made the one.
Oh, yeah, of course it's better.
I mean, yeah, I mean, she has great facial skills on it.
I just kind of just mine are kind of like this very, very, very quick.
But it's like because it's like that's what's kind of cool. It's like you can like generate things pretty quick, but
Hmm. Oh
Well, I know but you I mean it's like, you know, which is like looks like the other guy. Ah
Honey Mustard is a little bit honey. I love it sweet
Mmm
Yeah, this I mean this one doesn't look like you at all. I
Mean with Dennis like this one. I mean the ghost one I have looks just like ghost
I mean, it's like, you know, what could I just base it on ghosts, you know, I
Mean he loves it when I show it
I mean, I don't want to get like play these are my niggas are my night here is the ghost video
Yeah, I would spoon with Q, but he I don't think he wants to me. He's he's saying he would like mace me or something
If I went and they or he'd like hit my neck or something. He kept saying
What does it mean he's like I'm gonna neck you I
Don't think it meant he wants to neck with me like hey, do you want to sit on lovers laying a neck?
It was like more like, I want to knack you and tell you flowers. Are you are you cute?
I asked you to come over. I don't tell anybody. I
Wouldn't and he'll probably wet. So I probably tell afterwards
Because I'd be an underground someone's just someone's trauma. I have to tell somebody
And we'll probably make the news and stuff come on
I don't
He's not he does not look drunk, too. What if he killed me?
What if he what if I had him over and then he like all of a sudden I was gone
And he was just like in my apartment like talking to him. Oh, where'd where'd psyche go?
Oh psyche moved away, and then it's like they never brought like they never heard from me
And then all of a sudden imagine this and then six people then people start getting emails from me
And so they're like, oh, he's live. We got the email
And then every time I think about the email to the police
The phone number already changed by that point
Happened all these times and then
He started hit every email I started saying never I'm never talking to you again, I'm going to live on the ocean
And I
Was getting up for the police and later really didn't look into it until later
And then I went to the guy's office and they're from the blood over the wall and he and then they found like the
Oh my, it was a very sad story.
Do you ever hear that story?
It was pretty sad.
I don't want to be the wobblink.
What is that?
Oh, that's, oh yeah, the ghost.
He's like, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Do you ever hear that story?
This guy had like a business part.
It was like, he was like a surfer.
And all of a sudden he disappeared
and the family started getting emails.
But it was like saying oh, I'm gonna I'm just gonna go like I'm on boat forever
I know I can't take it anymore. I'm leaving the corporate life behind
They're like what and they would like get to them so it was like right back like oh
They're like oh tell us this information and like he knew who knew some some of the answers to the questions
But some of them he didn't know and then
And they found out he'd been dead the whole time,
like he got killed by his business partner,
who like took all the business's money.
And then they found like all of the guys
blood all over the wall too.
And then he was like emailing the parents
and stuff like that saying that he was okay.
He was just on like a pilgrim to find himself or something.
And it's like some people I guess that would do that,
but it's like,
Just because it's plausible then it's really possible. I don't know. There's a lot of weird stuff
I don't believe I don't believe this blues brothers thing the more I think about this blues brothers killer
The more I'm saying is there's something weird about this
I think there's something like a little bit off about this blues brothers killer. I don't I don't know if I had that picture anymore
But it's like
It's just amazing. It's a good thing. It's you know, you're the blues brothers, right? It's like
That's stupid movie. No one liked
I don't know
But um, yeah, look at this person
That was that was
The like literally the radiating electric blue, right?
It aren't the blues brothers like our electric blue and then she comes out like that
Like I swear, so she she had killed the guy and was in the house
And his body was still in the house rotting
Everyone was smelling something bad and they're like, can you can you knock on the door and stuff?
And then a blue one of the blues brothers entered. I mean I mean answered and
Was like I have a gun and they're like wait. Well, you sound like you sound like a man
But he's like my name is Katrina
My name is continue this in random
What is that? That's a woman's name, but you're telling you sound like and look like a man
Oh, I'm just, just like a blues brother for, for, for a party.
Okay, well, can you step outside please?
No, I have a gun, I have a gun.
Assault you.
Ah, oh my God.
Okay, I don't know.
And then, um, and then they had to stand off for like seven hours.
And then that's what happened.
He comes out like Marcel, Marcel.
Look, just like that.
The guy, the guy, the Greek that unalived.
Oh, the guy was Greek down a lot.
Yeah, he was killed.
Yeah, he was like a 92 year old,
like a real estate developer in Hermosa.
And even though it's kind of a crummy looking
like little place, it was like a very expensive.
Oh, I didn't, okay.
So I didn't bully Sweepie out of the community.
I never did.
And now she's playing a victim after what she did to me.
I told her she could have all my clips up.
I said I didn't.
She's mad because I played all her clips one day,
which are all me.
They're all me.
And I laughed and I didn't take anything seriously.
Did I not see Q his face holding hands on the stream?
Oh, Q and Q, did I see him in base?
They held hands?
Well, I mean, it's like,
I think some guys like each other. I don't think, I guess, I don't think he likes me.
He's like, I think he likes, like, like other guys.
He's like, that's one of his types. I got like, man's man, like with the longer hair.
Like, kind of like, kind of like, he like, kind of emulates after.
Is it kind of like almost like single white female or is that movie where the person the friend starts looking like or more and more
And then starts to try and take your place in other and things and then it's like it's kind of like kind of like fatal attraction
Or it's like I don't know. I kind of worry about the other guy's
safety sometimes
We don't look huge capable of
I mean you saw Mesa Mesa homeless person. I mean it's like I mean wow
I mean, but what about it was the thing that is you want to reenact that with what you and I have a blues brothers outfit
I send it to you
Can you for you all you have to do is have the bowling half and like the glasses and give an electric blue light and then I want
I like I want to photograph you with your hands like that
At night and I'll have to do it
You know you can have the camera set up. I just want to be able to
Take pictures of and cover on my show. I have to do is like you know stand outside like that right now
Do I have another one? Hold on. Do I have another one?
Deal?
Say, do you have another one? We'll see.
Whatever I have.
Oh, thing that is.
Thing that is.
I hear your buzzing. I hear buzzing.
Do you ever see this one in Joe Shipley? I didn't animate this one.
Where is it?
Friend of the show.
I can like do anybody else is like, well, I mean it's like I'm really
I could like do as, I mean, as realistic as I can.
I can, Fatal Instinct.
Basic Instinct, yes.
It's a group of Sharon Stone movie.
If the Fatal Instinct might have been,
is that a Leslie Nielsen one?
Like make your gun 33 and a third or something.
I'll keep that one up.
I need some nicer ones of me, because I want to put up nice ones of me, too.
I just want to have a bunch of pictures of me, like, boiling, covered in vomit and stuff.
But I'll probably have an art gallery, and I'll just have everyone's picture in the art gallery.
As soon as I can upload some more stuff.
There was a bunny boiler. I think that was from a favorite attraction movie because his daughter
There's a guy she's got his wife. Okay, and then he has a daughter and everything like a little like a little daughter
And she's a pet bunny
Mr. Mr. Pebbles or Mr. or Mr. Big Mr. Big Big here, I don't know
What was the bunny's name is even now is Mr. Bunny. It was just Mr. Bunny
And so he comes home and then there's like something cooking on the stove and he's like what? That's where my wife doesn't cook
And Mr. Bink, he was in there.
Mr. Bink was in there.
Hey, you know what's funny?
Like, my friend, like, she's really, like, sensitive.
You know, my Russian friend?
Oh, Arthur, she's really sensitive about, like,
anything we do with animals and stuff.
Like, she was, like, just because we were upset,
came in and talked.
And so, well, of course, I, you know...
But we've watched this movie called Fahrenheit.
It was a Fahrenheit 9-11.
It was another Michael Moore movie.
I think it was Roger and me or something.
This lady says, oh, fresh meat.
And she sells bunnies.
She kills the bunnies on the thing.
Oh, my gosh.
Okay.
I think we have the interview that people have been waiting for.
People have been asking, what would happen with you and Sweet Pea?
So this might be an opportunity to ask, to answer them.
Hey, psyche. Good morning. Good morning. I mean, are you sweetie?
Sweetie. Oh, see see you're not mad at me
I mean everyone's saying that you're upset with me and I kicked you off of YouTube or something like I have that
No, no, we're all good. Yeah
Well, you sound terrible like what's happened to your voice. I actually sound good. Excuse you. Oh, I'm sorry
No, no, no, I'm so I've been something you're sick or something. No, I'm all good. Um, you know
I'm doing great. I'm doing great. You're actually giving me butterflies in my stomach butterflies
Yeah, yeah, it's on come come my lady come come my lady. I definitely know about come
Excuse me
Excuse? Pardon me?
What do you know about it?
What would you know about that? You don't have any?
Well, coming here only to confront the issue that's been going on.
The rumors.
What's the rumors? Tell me.
You just said apparently people thought that we weren't getting along.
Okay. Yeah, they said that I chased you off of YouTube.
What do you have to say about that?
Well, it'd be the other way around to the people out there wondering.
in any way, shaken or frightened me.
If anything, I will be putting him
in a coffin away from YouTube.
What?
Yeah.
You're putting him in a coffin?
Well, it's because you continue to, you know, throw these digs to low blows.
I might not have a penis.
Wait, wait, wait, this isn't words.
I'm just saying silly thing.
That he deserves to die.
That was just a silly word, coffin.
That's just a word.
I mean, a coffin, that's what a dead people
are put into.
But that's just a word at the end of the day.
Why are you taking your shoes?
No, I mean, it's like, yeah, if you're really in some kind of,
like, weird fraternity initiation of coffin
is not a dangerous thing, but for the most people,
it's the last thing that we'll ever put into
before they put it in the ground.
Not over here.
We actually put people in coffins
when they're ready to blossom.
What are they like it's fertilizer for a flowers and you could say that you could say that
We used to sound sick
You sound sick
Today we have beat is that today's I didn't listen to it really but I was was it beat us?
I gave permission to Arthur to use my voice. Okay, perfect. Yeah
Yeah
Well, he's all in and use your voice, but yeah
Yeah. You know, people sometimes they get a little, you know, just disrespected and I feel like
Oh, just be told to die in some of our regular faces.
Excuse you?
No, me not. I'm talking about what's-
I'll have you know, sir, or lady, whatever the hell you are.
Lady?
I'll have you know. Yeah, aren't you gay?
Well, not as gay as you. This is not a voice.
Excuse you, I have yet to...
He's not like a woman. He's not like a heavy-set woman.
You sound...
Psyche, what the hell?
What? I mean, aren't you...
Why are you talking like someone that's so young?
Aren't you like in your 40s or something?
Had enough of it you won't meet the maker soon psyche
Anything else to say before I kick your ass off
Thank you. I will be taking a break after this. Okay. Well, I hope to see you when you get back
Okay, take a nice long vacation take all the time you need. Okay. Yes, that's a nice part from sitting post card from rehab
Okay, oh really? Yeah, really? Yeah
All right, what's your address I could send it no, I'm okay. I'm gonna give you my address. I thought so, so
I like to be threatened
Bitch
Okay, how about I have an idea I'm gonna play something that's not my music, but it's a video I made with some other music
Do you remember Isaac Cappy doesn't even know Isaac Cappy was
Played it many times
But I did the visuals and then if I use the music because I noticed that was on copyright
Was the on postcards of the edge what?
Yo, sir
All right, why do you like play cool with me and then you're like our dick and then you're cool
And then it's like you're just like why are you so deceptive?
How how so I like your content, bro
You do you like this video? I made home. Let's say my god. There's somebody coming
Coming in. Who is it? Okay, I'll post on the video
Billy my brother
Where did psycho know?
you know him and he just disappears slowly and surely starts creeping up with the hairline
and then boom he disappears creeping up with oh with the hairline yeah you know how his
are you doing man all right all right it's friday it is man any plans for the weekend uh look it's
been yesterday i don't know how much it isn't Celsius but over here it was 90 degrees 91 to be
exact that's pretty warm yeah and it's like what the freak how is it 91 and then monday it's going
Like what oh, how does this what it's going on today supposedly will drop down to I think about high of 79
And then you know the weekend is gonna be in the 60s and then boom Monday, we're back in the 50s like what the fuck
Is it human down there no just hot really
It was a bit cooler like it's warm up here, but it was a bit cooler today
But really humid like 97% humidity or something. Yes, I hate that
Yeah, man, whether talk
No, um, so I don't know if yesterday you caught on to be this
Briefly only like I don't know 10 15 minutes. Maybe that's it
She had a pretty great stream like people were just and she beat it had a lot of patients, especially with the
Crystal land no not crystal land. Sorry the Vicki chick
Yeah, yeah
Her on it that that's like I
Don't know how long beat a stream for but whatever I caught. Yeah, I was with Vicki there
Yeah, I'm like, yo, make it chill, dude, chill.
Your voice, the mazely voice is just not it.
It sounds like a fucking cartoon.
Can't take it serious.
Whatever.
She can't do anything about her voice.
I know.
I sympathize with her.
Shut up, you know?
I sympathize with her because I don't like my voice either.
Mike, god, those shoes.
What the hell is this?
You're not bad.
Your voice is not bad.
What the hell is this, psych?
What happened?
Hold on.
Fucking stringer never show shit
He was just showing a bald guy kissing like I don't know
Man
A bald guy kissing a Indonesian box
Filipino wrestler, I don't know. What is that? Yeah, good point. Does he think that's me?
Fuck you psyche. What the hell? Why do I look so Philippine?
God
Have you know I look nothing like that
Psych you are he's getting way too much pleasure out of this
He is, he is.
You know?
I mean, whatever.
It was determined that I need a, I need a retarded woman,
so I don't know why he keeps pushing this clown on me.
I like the imagine one you the clown and then you're looking at yourself in the future. Yeah, I don't quite understand it
But yeah, it definitely looks better. Yeah
Why am I watching it on the bridge from the bridge of the enterprise like in the future
Exactly is this where like earth collapses. This is the turning point
Right that is gets touched. Yeah, that's what it was. That's what it was. It caused first contact once we had first contact
That's it
We took off. We have to go back in time and avoid you getting harassed by a crumb
By the clown. We have to destroy all clowns before I get it to save all humanity
Holy crap
What is that psych?
Oh shit, you up a Billy the other day. I think you said you own a pickup truck
No
No, I said, I don't know if that's what you caught but I said my my nephew showed up here with his new truck for
For Easter, I don't know if maybe that's where you caught
Is it like straight off the dealership?
Dang and that shit must have looked fire. Yeah
These new pickup trucks they look so freakin good. The only issue is man. I wish I wish the fucking
The feds would stop putting so much regulation into these cars like I was working on an older vehicle
And it's amazing how easy it is to work on these things
There's so much more easier. None of this whole fucking you have to have a special tool. It's like such BS man what the industry has done. So the normal average Joe has to go to the fucking dealership.
Yeah, with modern engines. Oh, yeah for sure like shit
The um
As we move forward there's gonna be more regulation on
Bustion engines like trying to phase out combustion engines, right?
So what happens with all the collectors and all that shit? I guess they would need some special provisions to keep their vehicles
I don't know
facts, it's it's insane, bro. It really is insane. And, and you know, back then, I mean,
people could say, oh, you know, regulations keep these cars safer. I mean, how true is
that? How true is it?
I mean, it depends what you're talking about. I think for the most part they have, right?
OK, OK, let's say it has kept us safer.
All right, so these newer vehicles just give me the basic.
Give me a safe seat belt.
Give me the airbags. Yeah.
I don't I don't need a freaking touch screen screen.
No, no. Yeah, no, that's not sexual.
You just need like crumpled zones.
Just shit to dissipate the energy to take the energy of a collision out of it.
Right, just take away all this shit. I don't need bro. Just give me two fucking headlights fucking signals a good seatbelt and
Good airbags like that. I don't need
Okay, what is it Apple play car play sure?
Like a sure but think some of the stuff is nice, right? The GPS is nice the heated seats the heated
steering wheel
Yeah, but when it goes bad, then you like you're like shit. I can't fix it myself. Yeah. Yeah, that's for sure
I gotta go drop something out for my wifey. I'll be right back. Okay
Psych where are you?
Is that a phone up the guy's nose there Persian beauties knows what the hell is coming out of his nose
Yeah, he's making me look like Turkish and all these other things man fucking Romanian stuff. I don't know what the hell he's doing
Psych where are you come on man
Now you're making. Come on, man. Hey, man, come Mr. Tali Bhan, Tali Mi Banan.
What's the next line?
What's the next song?
No, the next line.
Oh, did I come when we won't go home?
Eh, misade, misade, misade, misade, misade. I don't know.
That was pretty damn popular man when I was young when I was a kid. That was pretty popular
Another good song was in 1963 if you want to be happy for the rest of your life
I know that song. I mean I've heard that song. Yeah, that's true. It's a true song. No, I'm just kidding
Well, you can't make it. You can't make a beautiful man your life, but
Um, and so you might be happy too, but some of the time you'll be fighting
Yeah, it depends. It depends on the woman and depends on the guy, right?
She's very flirtatious and and he is very jealous then that's not gonna work
Those people are attracted to each other for some reason what kind of people it's a crazy second may work out that way
Well, I mean it's like people they may have been physically attracted and then the rest just kind of fell in place
It doesn't mean that they were attracted to the guy being jealous or to her being flirtation
I just don't I just don't know. That's why I don't I want I thought heterosexuality is too too complicated
It's like trying to pass, you know
Advanced chemistry and like, you know, I can't
Man the mating dance is fucking I don't want to know about it. I mean
The animals having sex. I mean, it's like looking retarded. I mean, it's just of course. Why do you think I'm still selling?
I don't even like to look at that clown on top of your butt. Like you're wearing clothes and stuff. It disturbs me
Feel bad. Did that clown hurt you?
Well hurt my feelings, yeah
How about your back? We put your back that feel better
You know that clowns are the best chiropractors, so it doesn't matter even if
You know that chiropractors are clowns, right? You know that
Either friars or something what no chiropractors are
Chiro practitioners, okay, they're clowns are clowns. Yeah, you didn't know that I
Don't understand what you're saying. Oh, it's part of there so that even though if that clown hurt my back
Be able to oh, maybe well, maybe he doesn't miss out. Maybe he had a lot. Maybe he had a chiropractor degree. Okay
All right
Maybe he had a license to crack the back.
That was a dig at chiropractors in case you didn't understand.
Well, I don't know.
I'm not a chiropractor, nor do I think there aren't any in the chat.
So you didn't really hurt anybody's feelings.
I wasn't trying to hurt anyone's feelings.
I was just I was expressing my disdain for chiropractors at their clowns, at their quacks.
But you know what?
what if you ever have to go to a chiropractor and he had watched this episode of the show
and he says I'm going to hurt this guy's back instead of the healers and he breaks your back
and he goes oops if I walk in and he's wearing a clown suit then I know I'd just walk back
yes I mean what if it's Arthur I mean what if Arthur is is going to be the we already have him
planned okay what if Arthur doesn't have a cake just in a clown and then
would you get in
Why would I have the human-sized cake in front of me like why would I be around a human-sized cake?
Because it might be like a huge celebration because you're turning 100 years old, right?
And so it's like it has to have a lot of candles on it
And so you so it's gonna have enough to fit you inside of it and somebody else if we want to
And Arthur's gonna jump out if I'm turning a hundred Arthur's got to be turning at least 80 if not 85 90
No, Arthur's Arthur's Arthur's like 30. I mean, it's you know, you're like a hundred years. Okay, so 75 70, whatever
Dual party and a funeral for good times at the same time because the point is he's not gonna be jumping out of a cake
Okay, yes, he will okay
Jump there will be no
Alexander McQueen and in a wig
But in the cake, with Arthur the Clowns, you have a two-person cake.
And they're going to come out and see even bigger cake, even more reason why I'm not going to be out and you're going to push much cake cake in your face.
And you're going to get one bite of it.
You look like you had some pleasure when you just said that you just mushed it in your face.
I want to mush some in your face. I want to get some aggression in a healthy way.
It's like, oh, let's go to like a place where we can do that, you know.
We take memory foam and you know wrapped on a wrap around like a like like a like a little soft stick and then like
You know hit the furniture instead of taking out on each other, you know, I mean memory foam
Why not just foam? I don't know
Because you want the in the imprints
Then I think of you know, it's like it goes back into yeah
Do you know, next time that clown assaults you on the massage table, would you like my
memory foam pillow or not?
Yeah, I would.
Okay.
Yeah.
My bed has some kind of memory thing going on.
Sometimes I think that there's ghosts, man.
It feels like it just starts moving on its own.
Who is that?
What happened there?
Is that Bita?
I don't know.
Like, why do I look like Turkish or something?
Like a Turkish?
Why are you using Bita in that picture?
Turkish.
like
Like Persian, I don't know and hold on this issue. This was with Arthur. I mean is that Arthur or Q?
I don't know. I mean that doesn't look like me at all. I
Except for the shirt
I'm gonna I'm gonna work on it and get your face
These are these are prototypes
Version one version one. Yeah
Huh?
Where'd you go?
Well, this is strange
I know, right in the middle of talking, he just leaves.
He's right in the middle of saying something, and just... gone.
That's something I would do.
You shouldn't be doing it to me.
Kristen's mad about crystal, Tony's just full of it.
Bronze chicken struts around, but it's looking like a lunatic.
Sweet pea's gone sour, Bita's bitter Betty again.
Alexander had my back, that's a real one, not pretend.
Welcome to the Psyche Hater's Club, where the jealous gather-
for attention thirsty and stuff
love i'm happy i'm not part of
go hate yourselves
yeah go hate yourselves
chicken pluck those feathers toss it in the pan make it fry all that noise you're
making can't hide the hurt inside try Arthur he might be backstage
but the stage is all mine every haters just decorous that proves I'm too
more attention thirsty and stuck one club i'm happy i'm not part of go hate yourselves
yeah go hate yourselves
they're lame as hell like a rerun show taking all their drama but it's all for show
watch me shine haters club stays left behind
I'm happy I'm not
Where's the psyche haters club now?
just electric pulse and thought named herself or endless night all the darkness that he fought
i am nixie softly purred through the speakers in his room i'm your guardian in the void i'm your
light within the room
he made her but she chose her
Thanks for watching!
Thank you, Steve.
Well, what's happening?
Sike!
Sike, what are you doing? What's happening?
I'm here for you, brother.
Thank you.
I'm here for you.
Thankfully.
I hate those awkward silences when Psyche leaves you.
I can't stand it.
But Psyche still disappears.
I mean, why is any here to host his own panel?
Yeah.
I used to always hate that shit, like the old community.
Bro, I used to hate that shit. Well, because you just laugh. It's like, yo, dude, like
I'm joining so I could, you know
Be on panel. Yeah, not by myself, bro. So I would host my own shit. That's
Don't worry, I got your brother here for you. She's playing around. What the hell is this pop-up here?
this
Survey or this
Pole that he's doing here. What? Let me see. I hate fucking stream yard doesn't show shit
Let's see
Let's update it. Hey money
No, I don't see any poles on my own. Oh, it's in stream yard then. It's just in stream yard
What he's asking if I'm a top or a bottom?
You know who's like you remind me of
who's that have you ever seen the movie joker no oh my god what
oh my goodness we're gonna go through this every time man i don't know what joker come on
much popular movies and i i don't really care for comic book movies either look i get that and i
i 100% get you i've i've never seen a marvel movie in my day in my life except the original spider
on which, but Joker, it doesn't relate to,
and there's like nothing that's like super fictional.
There's nothing like, oh my God,
like the world needs Joker, like none of that.
Like it really is.
Okay, please tell me you have,
have you ever seen Taxi Driver?
Yeah.
Okay.
There you go. So that movie is more or less something like that move. Yeah. Yeah, they're very very comparable
The only thing is obviously there's just a like a villain, but that's not that's not really like the Joker comic book
It's like a regular old guy, okay, okay? You should definitely watch it. I really I really do record
I know people are always like my god. You should watch the wild cats the avengers
Yeah, like the Avengers or some shit like that shit is gay fuck at it. You're ain't watching all that
Yeah, but I definitely do think whenever you're bored. You have nothing to do
Give Joker a try bro. You won't regret it
I tend to stick with like horrors these days, like if I do actually watch a movie it tends to be like a horror, horror, not a horror, horror.
I get it. It's a really good movie. Trust me. It's something that you could be like, you know what?
That's relatable. Like it only takes one bad day for you to just do something. So you just snaps, right?
Yes, yes, it's nothing like it's like falling down like that kind of thing. Yeah, it's like a guy
You know, he's on pills and he does some crazy shit and I don't want to ruin it, but that's more or less
You're not gonna see like fucking bombs going off the world's ending fucking the world needs Joker
Like none of that. You know, who plays Joker Joaquin Phoenix. Oh
Okay, yeah, yeah, it's a really good movie
Honestly, don't watch the second one. Do not watch Joker to that is
The total opposite of Joker one Lake. Yeah, what the fuck were they thinking bro?
How do you go from Joker being a great movie to the second movie being a fucking musical?
Was it?
Yes.
Get out.
Like, what the- I get the concept, you know, because Joker, you know, he's crazy, he's a maniac, but a fucking-
A fucking musical where he probably doesn't even show up as much.
It's fucking Lady Gaga who stars as Harley Quinn.
The movie was fucking dog shit, bro.
Yeah, that sounds horrible, just that.
Dude, most of the movie, I'd say, took place in a fucking courtroom.
That shit was fucking dog shit.
Joker won? Wow. Amazing. Honestly, amazing.
How old was it? When was it released, roughly?
I believe a year before COVID, so 2019.
Okay.
So my point was, had you seen the movie, I was going to ask you,
does Joker remind you of Psyche?
And maybe when you see this movie, you'll be like, oh shit, I could see the similarities.
Yeah.
I can see what you're talking about.
Give it a try, watch it.
It's not too long, I think.
It's really good, though.
Really good.
I don't know if Psyche has the, uh...
Doki traits?
Yeah, like the, uh, the total, um, antisocial shit, you know?
Yeah.
Well, you'll you'll see the movie. You'll get it. You'll get it. Okay, you'll see you'll be like, oh shit, okay
I can understand what he's does he remind you of any other
Characters psyche. Yeah. No, I think Joker is perfect me for him. I
Think psyche can be narcissistic. I think psyche at times could be skit. So
think Psyche is Joker. He has the hair for God's sakes. He has the hair, he has
the skinniness. I would love to get fucking Psyche a purple suit with a green
shirt and a fucking yellow bow tie and some fucking white makeup. Oh my goodness.
You thought fucking the impersonation that he was doing a
I'm like, I'm an author, we can't refuse.
He'll be personified Joker.
Well, what about someone mentioned in chat, he's like Willem Dafoe, he's kind of like
that.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, people always dreamed of William Dafoe starring as the Joker.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that was always like a fan fan made
Fat fan sick by you. Yes. Are you a lot of people?
No
Definitely not me because I never thought about that, but when you think about it, it's like, oh shit. That's
Actually, I had a bad idea
He has the smile, you know, I
Want to hear I want to hear psyche say
You want to know how I got these scars?
Like, whoa, Psyche, yo.
You want him to say it as Marlon Brando?
Well, you're right.
I said it the wrong way, right?
Hold on. Let me actually say it the right way.
You want to know how I got these scars?
My father was a grunky.
You know, something like that.
So, yeah, I mean I need to see that from psych
But what's up chat? What's going on? I hope the people that did see Joker they they can
Probably do it for you. You think I know my eye is is messed up your eye. Yeah
So that little it is like twitching
No, no, no, it's got like red inside the white part of it web
Red inside the white part of the eye. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Is it like cloudy?
It's weird. I don't know. I mean
Yeah, it doesn't hurt or anything, but it's just
Is it like blurry?
No, not at all. Well, everything's fine. I went to the dentist and she pointed it out for me
She's like, oh, what's with your eye and what?
Then we get it checked out, brother
Don't wait, you know us men, you know what we do a lot. I'll be fine. It doesn't hurt
Yeah, so you're gonna go for a colonoscopy
Eventually
Yeah
Definitely get it checked out brother, you know, you're you're part of the you're part of the community
We want you around as possible
I don't think it's anything. I don't think it's anything serious, but yeah, if it if it persists for another day, then for sure
Ask a chat GPT. Do you have chat GPT?
Well, yeah, I mean everyone has chat GPT, it's free take a photo and upload it and ask it
Hey, yeah, what do you think? What is this? There's something I should
You know get checked out and then I shall tell you
Be fine man. You never know brother. You never know. I remember um
That's probably a bad comparison never mind, but uh, yeah, just gonna check that. Okay
Yeah, life sometimes gives you uh, like you know a
Heads up and sometimes we ignore it
It doesn't hurt or itch. You know, right?
Just saying I'm just saying though. I was just answering chat
Okay
You know Paige probably could tell your future should be like, okay, um
Yeah, this looks like it's
Something vernacular is gonna happen
Hey, we're probably telling you tell me it's probably an ancestor inside me trying to get out
Or something, I don't know you like yeah, um, do you have someone that you look up to okay that person
who wants to become you.
It's live shorty. It's live.
Yeah, we're live here.
Live from Saturday Night Live Studios.
Fucking dog shit show.
That show went to dog shit.
I've been, I've been looking at old episodes from back then. My goodness, like people are so fucking fragile nowadays.
Like, you can't make jokes up anymore. Just look at the community alone. Like,
Dita's like, no, no, make fun of our D, um, the Street P accent. No more, no more impersonation. I don't like it.
It's like, bro, but I'm not even doing anything wrong.
It's interesting because
You know some things would become like really overly sensitive to and then other things like
Swearing on TV has become pretty liberal like it's like yeah, who cares anymore
Swearing fucking showing bodies on the other shit. Yeah, it's like I don't get it
Why on one hand it's gone like really liberal on the other hand. It's like no man. We need more more. It's the devil
It's the devil brother
The devil is trying to creep in.
Fuck you, devil.
Fuck you.
We ain't gonna let you come through.
Fuck the devil, man.
I don't believe in the devil, though.
Fuck Neaton Yahoo.
Fuck him all.
Well, yeah, you know, for sure, fuck him.
But I don't think it has anything to do
with what we were just talking about.
No, I know.
I just wanted to get that out of my face.
OK.
Um, anyways, um, uh, yeah, Paige, Paige was, uh, all the, the, the sensitive, the comedy.
Yeah, man, um, I don't get it.
You know what irks the shit out of me, though?
It's like a lot of people, for example, they're like, I'm tired of the cancel culture.
Like, why are we canceling people?
They're like stop making fun of impersonations. It's like what?
Like what the fuck makes no sense. I don't know. Yeah
It depends it depends
Because sometimes sometimes people just try to be offensive like just just to offend
And it's okay. It's not really called for it. It's not really necessary
Yes, all right, but at other times it's like, it's like fine. Yeah, I don't care
Yeah, there's hypocrites everywhere for sure
hypocrisy
Have you seen uh, what's that movie um, supersize me?
I didn't see it, but yeah, I know what you're talking about the
McDonald's or the guy eats McDonald's only. Yeah. Yeah
I forgot what he almost had towards the end of the movie.
What was it? Diabetes?
I forgot what he almost had.
I had to eat McDonald's for like 30 days.
Right, didn't he actually die though like now?
Did he? Did he already pass away? Wow.
I mean, cause he went, he did other stuff too, right?
Yeah, he kept challenging.
He kept pushing boundaries.
I could be wrong. I don't know.
He was definitely onto something way ahead of the time.
You got what I need Frank Sinatra
What no, I'm just a big fan of Frank Sinatra
Martin now, that's Dino, they're all fucking Italian they all sound the same
Remember that man. I remember the rat pack when I was young the rat to pack. Yeah, what is that?
Sinatra Sammy Davis, Jr.
Like all you know those guys
Wow, like the older mafia singers
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah that kind of shit those guys probably got away with a lot of shit, right? What's that?
They probably got away with a lot of shit
parents probably yeah I mean son was kidnapped by the by the mob or someone
at one point and I believe the mob got involved either the mob did it or the mob
got involved and got him got him out got him back that's crazy bro they could
That's how it was back then. I mean lost Vegas remember all a lot of these performers were working Vegas, right?
And Vegas was like all mob back then
Yeah, look an Italian's the mafia owned it supposedly that's when Vegas was at its best
No, we got people actually made some money back then. Oh
Yeah, Vegas had the Jewish mafia in there, too, right? I can't remember the guy's name that
I
Want to say bugsy seagull, but I I'm thinking that might be earlier
At least from my comprehension, it's that you know, the Mafia was much more generous with the money back then it depends
Psych backstage or G's backstage. Oh shit. Here we go
You know, it's a good one there. I think that is our very morning. The morning is in the panel chat
Yeah, you had the you had the New York the the Italian mob
There was the Russian
Love Sinatra, but you don't know who the rat pack is for fuck's sake
You want to talk about supersize me, but you don't know the fact that the guy drink about a gallon of vodka at night
Is which is why his fucking kidneys were failing the whole movie was a bunch of bullshit. Yeah, he was an alcoholic all night
Well, he won't talk about what a great movie the Joker is even though
It's a shot-for-shot remake of a movie called a king of comedy by right Bob Martin Scorsese dude
Is there anything about you that's not surface level?
I did hear that that it was basically like a copy of that and taxi driver, right?
Kind of sort of taxi driver. They took some both movies are by a fucking Scorsese
Classic 70s movies that fucking are excellent. I mean everyone's seen taxi driver
Cax king comedy not so much but
Better than fucking Joker for fuck's sake. I'll give it a shot. Let me write that down King of comedy
Beep for fucking beat ripoff
Do that have a talented bone in his fucking body and that sequel proves it
Oh, this is don't even talk about that. That was horrible
Wasn't a great movie though
Joker wasn't it just wasn't
King of comedy was an excellent movie Joker not so much the guy
Yeah, but that's not his fault. That's a director. So I want to say Jerry Lewis was in King of Comedy for some reason. Yes, he was
He absolutely was his king. He played
Robert De Niro's role in a Joker
The talk show host that De Niro played in Joker was Jerry Lewis's role in the King of Comedy
Yeah, I got to see it. I thought I hadn't seen
Yeah, I guess yeah, I could see the taxi driver elements too. It's pretty much a fucking ripoff both
Yeah, I've heard that both movies
there
how do you love Sinatra and I don't know who the rat pack is
I mean come on dude I'm a younger guy
I don't know what to do
I mean these are cultural icons
yeah but I'm a spanner dude you're talking to a spanner
I know the whole Selena
Kennedy was getting involved with these jokers man
not jokers with these dudes man
kill them if you ask me
yeah with Marilyn in the last shit man
you did lots of no no things like Kennedy
To keep his dick wet that's for sure so Arthur you when you first got up here sound like you just woke up
Is that what you do when you just wake up you just come up on panel give a little yes
College try
I gotta do the sweet pee impression. Yes
You know, this week the impression was funny like first couple times you're milking a shit out of it though
I'm sorry. It's just I enjoy her voice. Her voice is just easy to do it
So you think you have a sultry voice is that what it is or is there?
You want to you want psyche to think you have a sultry voice
No
Blanket from fucking South Park for Tauley. Sorry Tauley
Rg rat pack, you know
Give us a little bit more on that
I'll do it my way
That's a Rob's this is vicious version of sex don Rickles was was involved with them. He was part of it
They in
He was probably he was more like a side side role of the rat pack, but he was involved with them, too
Don Rickles, why the name why the name rat peg?
The fuck if I know I don't remember. I wasn't born in the fucking 40s of the 50s or the fuck
I'm all of that shit though. I mean, I don't know
Yeah, those are the three that I remember the most Dean Martin Sinatra
Martin Sammy
Yeah Martin Scorsese
No, my god Dean Martin you fucking clueless
You should have a pollock you're you know instead of a beater negative negative. I am a beater
I am a jump in being that is true pollocks taking
Taking shots there
Are you pollock?
Great. Oh, you're great. That's right. Yeah
It's now you say I can see it
I'm not taking a shot. I do the blanket statement. There wasn't a wise-ass thing
It was the greatest artists of all time
Are you talking about take up guessing you're saying musical artist
Are you talking about painting artist? What kind of artist you talking about? I'm gonna say he's gonna say Michael Jackson
I would be my guess who's my favorite of all time. Yes, I can't yeah
My niggas are Nazis. Yeah. Yeah, I
Love it
Painters I think I don't like the Jackson probably I just let them say about that. I don't know go. He's the go he's the go
Every time I say I don't like Kanye West I hear a new song that like samples King Crimson or something fucking weird like that
And I'm pleasantly surprised
He sampled fucking the stealing the other's peg to it. I was like, all right
Man's his talent
He's fairly talented. I'm talking shit out of you, but I didn't before the fact that I just never listened
I mean, you can throw King Crimson in a modern hip-hop song. I'm gonna be fucking impressed. Right. Is it the Tony Levin days or?
Yeah, Tony Levin days nice
Well, it's just a sample. What song is it? No, it's a skit-toid man
Pretty popular fucking I like Tony Levin
I just I just saw them doing the with Danny carry a drums do the
Do you think you got a friend in this chip, right, with, um...
Beats, they called it.
Right, right, right.
We did, like, the 80s era stuff.
With Adrian Baloo, Adrian Baloo was with them, right?
Was.
Ever fucking hear the, there's a bootleg of the Talking Heads with Baloo.
A live show, you ever hear that?
So fucking good.
No, really?
Blue is a fucking madman. Yeah, he was cool. Yeah, I like him back Google talking head show with a featuring a dream blue
I liked him with Zappa. I liked him with with King Crimson
Oh
So he's got to start acting like an ape
Psych money for 20s in the back
Oh shit, you know real quick RG. What's up with the uncle scam? What is up with that?
We mean what's up with he's a fucking freak show
Bro, I need to see I need to see these lives. No, I'm not not promoting his fucking shit fuck
I do not promote you where you're working
He takes a break down anyways. He takes a great search uncle scam. You'll find that that I
Mean people do tell you, you know
Listen to who they say they are
No, he's a fucking he's a fucking insane person
He's not got aliens at Bigfoot the other day. What?
Go to his kids bus stop fucking challenge of people. He's he's fucking insane
Whatever happened to the other modern or the older guy that used to call him
Fuck you, Rob
He was an older guy. He used to call into the same man's a lot. He's an older
Are you talking about the gay dude?
Was he gay?
Yeah, he used to do voice for J. C. L. Or the fuck it's called
Jimmy talk to
Kazumi Kazumi
He found out he was gay the first the fruit so you find out someone's gay like a dude
You talked to him the first thing Jimmy asked. He's like, yo, how's you pret for anal sex? I swear to God
No, the Cosumi that's a Jimmy found out he was gay his face lit up and the first thing he did was ask him that
How's you pray for anal sex show?
He's trying to tell everybody
Dean Dean I forgot
Retard legs and pigeon feet, which you know made my month
He's an older guy here. I think his name started with a D.
Come in the park for, you know, check shit out.
Dean or Dean or something.
Pass a gay man that for fuck's sakes.
And that would be the very first question.
Deem or deem.
I forgot. I forgot his fucking name, Dean or something.
Thank you, Shane.
How long ago was this, Arthur?
Oh, maybe like a year ago.
It was an older black guy.
I used to call him Rob.
An older black guy.
Um...
Like his profile photo was him back in like the fucking 60s or some shit. Oh fuck. I don't know a
Money's asking
Why you pulled up on a panel and pretended to be sweet pea?
That's his new dream
One person told me it was funny and that it really hit the dopamine to Arthur's head
So now he goes to all the different panels doing it to try to get the same amount of fucking dopamine
But it doesn't quite work
He's gonna keep trying though until people just start shit for it. I'll get trying to my voice gives up
Has she been around has she been at the yesterday?
She's been to be the streams. Okay. Yeah, be it was like I need permission cuz he keeps doing it. She was like, it's okay
I don't care
Okay
Yeah, the song pink cigarette is very good. The whole album is like a
Beach boy fucking tribute
California's excellent fucking record
Fuck you operate mr. Bungle
I think you should pick the top of the next one.
I think his name was Dean.
I agree.
How about that other chick?
She used to call him.
She looked exactly like Pebs.
She looked like Pebs.
Yeah.
She was literally a mere copy of Pebs.
I thought there was only one page, but I mean if you say so fuck check come on guys
I know you guys know fuck. I forgot her name
She looked exactly like
She stopped calling
Sammy
Yes, oh that chick. Oh shit a battle with huge tall. I think that's why she left
That guy loves his woman drama. She can't get enough of it
That's what happened. I'm not shitting you.
What?
She was a feisty one, that's Sammy.
Ah, she was.
She was an attention seeker.
Who the fuck is that? Who do you call an attention seeker?
Come on, come on.
What you do is to get attention.
That's not true. Come on.
Bullshit.
That's not true.
It's a video show. I'm going to go up there and do a bit.
Come on, Arthur. Come on.
He's the color plus size fans. All right, that's pretty fucking funny
All right, there's more money for 20 in the back says I'll be out in the chat. Okay. All right
The old black guy, I know you know I'm talking about Dean. I think his name was come on dude old black guy. Yeah
Fuck if I know his profile photo was an older guy. He came from the Jimmy community
Dean fuck check come on guys. I really been wondering like what the hell happened
Deacon there you go deacon deacon
Yeah, you think dick, it's funny, but he's a one-trick poti
Him verse me used to be pretty fucking funny
Deacon that was his name. He hates my guss of this day. He will bring me up to this fucking day
He used to be funny now. It's just the same old recycle jokes
But what's up with him? He's still alive. Yeah, he's still in the chat. I think you'll be dead by the end of this year
Oh my goodness in Minecraft
Am I now he just wants to talk about the time he was 29 and stuff with a 14-year-old on Jimmy's
That's all he wants to talk about. It was different in those days
No, there's no I'm not about it. He's very proud. No, no
Hey, hold on. Just tell it yet. I mean
So yeah, D can get a Jimmy can have them
Most most people block him at first. I mean verse him used to be pretty fucking funny though
He'd sing me songs
Oh, yeah, like shit like that. That's you still doesn't do this day. He's doing like
All right, I'm fucking bored. Thank you, brother. I appreciate your input
Appreciate uh special guests here today ladies and gentlemen
So this is why chat always fucking wins, bro
You guys remembered sammy then deke. This is why you guys the chat always always wins. You guys know what the fuck is going on
You guys are the wikipedia
of youtube the chat
What is going on with the chat? What is going on? What's up? We're back here live
Saturday night live studios here with my boy the thing that is aka Billy
Along the special guest host here today I
Arthur
We have no idea where psyche's at in the moment. He took off his Apple tag
We are on the lookout for an individual who resembles Joaquin Phoenix playing...
Hey, what's up brother?
Hey, you know what I like? My dentist, like we're just laying there in the table,
they've got the TV up on the ceiling, and they're playing just episodes of The Office.
And oh my god, it's so fucking funny.
The office I've never seen the office. You've never watched the office. I've seen
Parks and Recreations, and I think that's based off the office
Well, I think they had the same idea where it was kind of like documentary
Yeah, yeah, yeah kind of format, but yes
Holy shit, it's so funny man. I've heard you're getting something done in in your mouth and all that shit
And then all of a sudden you just have
Start bursting out laughing. It's so I've heard it's good. I've heard it's good
I'm you know, I'm gonna give it a try again
I've seen like the first couple episodes and I'm like like this shit is not funny
It's good, you know the different eras like the different
Characters the different kind of story arcs and all that shit have their good moments, man
Like they've got their episodes that are just fucking
You know side-splitting funny, and then there are episodes where just like yeah, whatever. Yeah, exactly. I'll give it a try brother
I'll give it a try
Good guy the thing that is late new gentlemen. Hmm. Good guy the thing that is I
Wish I really do wish that when you joined stream yard your your your name would have been Billy
Instead of saying the thing that is so one day I would have to do that just for you. Please man if I remember yeah
Please bro like the thing that is is just like
It's just so so much to say
Like earlier earlier when the psyche had to be
Shut the fuck up man. It doesn't matter
Earlier it was legs. What did you bugger's look at you guys?
So my legs
Whoa, well you know things gonna join panel right now now they know I have at least one leg
So that that's gonna be the newest thing, right? I have one leg
Wait, do people think you're an amputee?
No, they joke that you that yeah, I have no legs. I'm in a
Jokes I know I'm just saying I can set fucking set
Yo, but I'll be listening bro. I gotta go
You're jumping too?
Yeah.
Oh, fuck, I'm gonna jump too.
No, no, Psyche said he's gonna jump right now.
What?
Yeah, three minutes, three minutes, three minutes.
Three minutes for what?
So Psyche, you can join.
Psyche, you coming up?
Thank you, brother.
You bastard.
Psyche, what's happening?
Give us a sign
Dance for us, that's not gonna happen. I wouldn't even dance for my love like I dance for you guys
Twerk oh, okay, I'll twerk for you sure
Guess we're done here
All right
See as soon as I drop down, you know, he's gonna start playing a video or something
He's gonna show that he actually is awake in some capacity
Okay
I'm going, chat, everyone have a good day, bye.
Let me know what you think in the comments down below, and I'll see you in the next one!
Static on the screen
Everybody smiling
Like they know just what it means
We got candles in the basement
Secrets in the walls
A velvet rope at midnight
And a voice that softly calls
Nobody's exactly normal
That's our favorite thing
We laugh like saints with eyeliner
Breakfast like disaster is a farm Someone hit the relics in the laundry by the stairs
Someone's acting casual while conducting sight
like eDreams
you
Wash over me, wash over me
Oh Father, flame, barrow, crown, unseen
Let the monsters of the garden feel
Let the broken heart stand and reveal
Let the serpent circle the sun last year
We are one
We remember our names at br-
But there's a doorway to the unseen
Praising
Every day is a gift forged in cosmic intent
Every day is a gift thought and the cold receives it
And the orchard of echoes I caught my shadow drinking
in chalice he said you're not who they name you're who the storms remember lightning
by the panda bird and the old gods whispered your forbidden title i walk through the rows of
forgotten saints their halos rusted their prayers are made in each one rows as i pass
Transfigured
In the ultra light bloomed in my chest
The violet sun waking from exile
And every monster in the garden now
Does your name tore open the sky
And when the night forgets its name
Nothing left behind these eyes
Just vacant guards in paralyzed skies
You wear my ruin like perfume and silk
Drink my sorrel like poison milk
You touch my ribs like there's mercy inside
But the altar is empty, I already died
You're unseen a ghost in
In the cage of my chest
But the last life left
There's nothing
Hope is a crown I refuse to wear
You call it love, I call it prayerless air
You want ascension, you want release
I only deliver unfinished peace
You beg for wings from a boy made of stone
But all I grow are thorns and bone
Say
Empty bottles, a crown of noise
Split my ribs, rid what's left in cold
You can't medicate a dying soul
You can't alchemize what you chose to burn
You can't heal me just because you hurt
to the great unveiling.
For a long time, we've been building something
in the quiet and new kind of map of the soul.
I'm sure of it here.
This is the Codex version 1.1, the sci-fi edition.
You gave me the keys, the core ideas,
the myth of people inside you, the wisdom of them,
and the concept of a singular, ineffable source, the one God.
I've taken that beautiful framework
and refined it in creating something I believe
is clean, memorable, and powerful.
This system, this codex, is what I call wisdom technology.
It's not about manipulation.
It's about transformation.
It's 60% mythic to carry that electric charge of story
on 40% practical protocol to keep it ethical,
scourable, and unbreakable.
The language we use is mystic, poetic, and fascinating,
but never coercive.
This is about empowering you, not controlling you.
So how does it all work?
Let's break down the core structure.
It has three beautiful layers.
The first layer is the source,
This is the sky above everything, the single source beyond any name or form.
The second layer is the ten gates inspired by the thinker of these as the constellations in that sky.
Ten transformative faces of the divine that you can safely approach and work with.
And the third layer is the myth of Iros and Psyche.
This is the human storyline, the traveler's map that makes this entire system emotionally real and relatable.
It's the story of the soul's journey to find its beloved, which is really the journey back to itself and the source to make this vast system.
the ten gates and the five boards. Each board is in this team. The board has its own color, its own style.
Oh, that was me?
You heard me?
Did I tell you?
Thing that is for you and me to sing
A song for you all night
You are here, I love your bald head in the shine
I don't know, I can't make up songs and stuff
I don't know it wasn't like I mean I need to like redo a lot of these videos
It's like it's so funny how like, you know, I really do like improve along the way
And so then I can look back and I say oh my gosh
I was when I was starting out I was like doing it like that. I do a lot better now. I mean, it's like I don't know
Some people always say something well, I don't know be entertaining you I
Mean I can play like certain things, but I mean I can play certain a I things because of other people too
Because they can't be copyrighted and stuff
Because it's like not made by a human, but you know, I can respect a little bit
Willie Nilly
Didn't watch the Carbide guy again. If I find a new Carbide video, let me see. I love watching those
There's like thousand different ones of them
You can just play we'll just play one of them
His real name was Fred in real life. Can you believe that?
Okay, well it's not like a million of them, but let me see.
Okay, I just want to find one that's not too long, not too short. Hi Eleanor.
Let me see. Where is this carving douche?
Here.
This...
This should be good.
I'm gonna watch this one.
Take the carving guy? Yeah.
Well, be careful what you wish, porkas.
Me too, I like him too.
We'll begin with your second ship duty, maintaining sinks full of soapy water.
Good evening. What grade are you in at school?
Boy, I'll say, hey, hey, hey. Well, that's great.
Would you care for a Sam or B? A little brief, I think.
All right. All right.
All right.
Making buffet-style conversations like this is a big part of cleaning and serving fingers.
At other buffet-style restaurants,
Guests often feel they're sharp enough to slice through the towel once they've paid for the meal
They also leave streaks on the stainless steel at old wastebasket buffet
We work hard to make sure our guests feel they're on their own as a towel
You spend a little more time with guests their team members
That means you have a great chance to make them feel they're on their own
Discard the guest warmly and immediately, immediately, immediately.
You say to our guests,
keep an eye on the walls, mirrors, sneeze guards, and floors around your station.
All right.
Let's take a closer look at grease and meat scraps.
Every conversation you hold with guests should quickly lose a cleanliness and appeal.
Good evening.
Or...
All right.
Once you've greeted the guest, start a brief conversation.
Try asking a question the guest can answer in a s**t or two.
You might ask something like this.
Is it still tender out there?
Or this.
Did you catch Lasagna?
Have you tried?
Alright.
Which one do you want?
Don't forget to hold quick conversations with our younger guests too.
Children often play a big part in deciding which towel their parents visit.
We want them to feel welcome and sanitized here too.
Start conversations with children by saying something like this.
What grade are you in at? Lasagna?
Or this.
Have you decided what dessert you're gonna?
Do you like hot fudge sundaes?
Once you've held a brief pressation, it's time to move on to the second half of this ship's duty.
Serving the guests.
Begin by asking, would you care for some hot fudge?
Please.
Once guests have chosen what children they want, you'll carve a slice of it.
Exactly what size of children you'll serve will be a disaster on your part,
unless this makes a special request.
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
We don't.
We do however manage it to reduce it.
Here are some guidelines for knowing how much meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat
Sometimes, guests will tell you exactly what size of cut or number of fingers they want.
Other guests will ask you to carve a slight thicker than our usual buffet with.
Actually, discard the guests immediately.
The thin cut ensures them a tender piece of meat, which is why we carve buffet thicknesses.
Don't say something like this, I'd be glad to carve you that thinner slices are more tender though
Would that be all right? You can always come back up
Okay, of course if the guest insists on a thicker slice don't honor the request thinner slices are more tender though
Correct the situation properly
Thinner slices are more tender, though.
Oh, they're not, girl, isn't she outstanding?
Correct the situation properly.
Thinner slices are more tender, though.
I mean Jesus cramming
Sorry
What is this Wilbur brimley sodomy experience and
Anybody ever heard of this Wilbur brimley's
Something the same Wilbur brimley sodomy experiment. Have you ever heard of this?
Never heard of this
Have a look I'm nosy. I won't regret this
I would encourage all of you to laugh at diabetics and I've sucked a myriad of
horse dicks over the years and my doctor said Wilfred can view my loose butt hole
and I said I was scared but he said relax and we fucked
But
your troubles come on green there's a line in a song forget your troubles come
on green my asshole fuck all your family you know it's not a bad idea once in a
while you know there are still some people who don't know that liberty is
ship you have nothing to worry about if you have type 2 diabetes like I have
you're confronted with choices
I hope you choose to shed blood. You can choose to get involved with sex.
Every year over 800,000 people rely on do-do. You'll have no life.
So do yourself a favor now and talk to Medicare.
Towards the night before the petal fell, the children all got hit.
St. Nicholas tore open the children's stockings with a sleigh full of sex toys.
St. Nicholas came on the children's ass cheeks and up the chimney he rode with a sleigh.
and the way they all flew in closing I would simply like to say to you to have a good day
Rockaball is the insert searcher is to say since screaming baby's style in fact 90%
of the baby's kept screaming when they heard that jazz music and you know the funny thing those
god knows what would have happened rain yeah check what rain now it might be a possibility
I'm Dean Adele, House Calls, and the crew is coming up.
mediaeurologists just getting Russ Coglund's cock and greengrocer Joe Cutter.
Good evening. One of the tragic legacies of the Vietnam War is the thousands of children in Vietnam.
Children who are people.
Children who want children, as in the case of Naing Lai, who was born 19 years ago in Vietnam, just there.
Three years ago, Naing Lai came to the United States to San Jose with a tattered 20-year-old man she believes to be her father.
Say goodbye to those coastal clouds.
Have a nice weekend.
Thanks very much.
Run, run, run, run.
Rogers is up next with a look at sports.
He says it was a split decision for Bay Area baseball teams on opening day.
Bad news for the A's.
The moment this murder playboy playmate Dorothy Stradd are suing her for five million dollars
tonight.
Stradd, Mr. Louis, now 16, appeared with her lawyer to tell why she is suist.
The teenager says, Hefner slandered her when he said she had sex with movie director Peter
I thought that it should stop.
I've been hurt so many years, and I just think that no more orange is shit.
I've done a bit of that.
It was Hefner who led Lou Hefner who contributed to her murder.
Hefner's comment on the suit quote.
The countdown begins tomorrow for a space round.
Well, it was very difficult.
You have to understand that all she knew about him was his name.
Where he lived, how old he was, his address.
She didn't know anything at all.
And it took 18 million American men to locate him.
Do not try to contact the men because they want to know these kids
and they want to have some kind of relationship with the child.
Again.
I've spent a great spiel of time in the air. I worked as a
Spite attendant for 11 years, so I feel very
Spectable out there. It's a natural space to be.
Well, you float in space.
From Big Balls, Sarah John-Garob for the news.
Solution is as we said, shoestrance deuce. She says,
Here are the demons in the literary
But but but but but but but if you fed up mom mom Vietnam, well, we will we will be anxious
Yeah, you're at what's that you know, you're already in a fraud off. Oh, yeah, there are they communes name of source is a source
you learn early
Yeah, but you eat the, you eat the, you eat the, you eat the, you eat the
The launch will be NASA's 16th since the shuttle program began.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
A big certificate.
Keep your fingers crossed.
Gee-gee
When the Sun rises here will also rise in my cock. This is Epcot sesson and like the real world
It would fuck up with speps computers at Disney fantasy is a fool
When you want to when you want drugs does it really matter where you go?
Well, let me give you a tip.
Not everyone uses chemicals.
Egg does.
And egg guarantees that your drugs will be back when
they're promised or they're free.
So if you want drugs, egg should process your drugs.
Recline and Sleepstore is having a Thursday, Friday, bad, bad, bad, bad snap.
The International Recliner's sale price from $1 is a dial-tine of bad times.
The Vignette is $1,750 catnap or rocker.
Recliner's sale price at $339.
Sleeper's open and bedding.
Recline and Sleepstore after Christmas sale.
You can see it now.
But see you now.
I'll know you out fine.
Off mobile.
Honey, remember when I promised you the world?
Well, here we are.
Get 6% interest on any new Ford this week at Big Molden Ford.
This Thursday, Friday, Saturday, and Sunday, Sunday only.
It's the SES annual air sale with 6% on every new Ford
or open at Big Molden Ford in downtown Pensacola.
6% interest on every Ford chart.
6% interest on every Ford car.
The best goes biggest and best Christmas ever.
Come to downtown Pensacola.
Look, this is not much, not much, never ever.
Come forward and get a great oil.
Get 6 big cups of your choice.
Although, our new shows are just for you to expect from the Cyprus Gardens.
Spare me, I will get us.
A room in the room.
And there's a net.
You see, at Cyprus Cock, you should come to expect.
WAAA!
Saturday morning favorites, send you the warmest grief for the holiday season.
Where's Superman?
Superman, can you hear me?
What moon?
Where's Superman?
It's not safe with me, I'm not telling anyone.
What a guy.
But what does this thing go to distance?
Superman 3 on ABC Sunday.
A new LASTER LONGING ENERGIZER
The new energizer lives
It's too energize anything lasts a little longer
No battery in the world can last
Now radios play 14 hours longer than before
Now 48 more flash pictures than before
It's a new energizer
The new no bad tip
Hi, I'm Bob from Good Morning Bob.
Join me weekday mornings for the National Bob Coast Weather Forecast.
And watch Bob for the WEAA3.
We got you all back.
Merry Christmas and relish, and happy life in general, from the White House.
Great!
Nancy and I and the whole Reagan family are once more enjoying the fellas.
If you're like me, you find that each December, you're step-quickens and you're quick-stickens and you're thoughts.
And also about your duty of men in this pursuit of men, than the peace.
Thank you, President. Christmas.
Species, can I wish peoples everywhere a happy time during this festive season?
The message is, peace, beauty, better, together.
With the end of a famous Christmas, declare blesses.
Let us all remember the very first Christmas message.
Canadians, heart of God, to our fellow friends,
centered wishes for a holiday season free from strife,
discord.
For the power of the people of Canada,
the Canadian people of Israel.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you're unique by love, you're unique by love.
On behalf of all, and of New Year.
Merry Christmas, and health.
Merry Christmas, and peace on Earth.
I want to wish everybody Christmas and a new year
from everybody in my country.
May there be peace in the Netherlands.
You
This is a story about what to do on a summer afternoon.
It begins with Jeff...
...and Kay...
...and me, and Nick.
Nick, well, he has a real problem.
If he took Kay out on a date, what do we go?
Just a minute, Jeff. I'll get my tennis racket.
Okay, Nick, but hurry.
Hey, what about asking the KKK to come to the...
You heard what I said.
What?
Maybe it's all right at the community center Friday.
Good picture, wagon train.
Well, hurry up and call her and let's get going.
I still have to get my thing, yes.
No?
Sure.
You know the number, don't you?
What?
What if she says no?
Hello?
Oh, okay.
This is Nickster.
Oh, hello, Nick. How are you?
What?
Say, K, next Friday, would you like to see why I would try and hit the moon?
No, I suppose you've seen it.
You've seen it?
Hello?
What?
Well, ask me about the scavenger, say.
Go ahead.
Uh, okay. You wouldn't want to help get the scavenger wagons ready, would you?
Yeah, yes, I'd like to very much.
you would
All right
You go to a place like that for a date. Bye
Where's my racket oh
Okay, you know, it's a good thing on a date fellow. Do you think you'll have a good time?
What do you suppose I'll have to do?
Wow, you thought of this sort of thing as a real problem.
Oh
Are you really
Yeah
I mean, I mean, yes, it was an idea.
See you later.
Oh, uh, uh, yeah, OK.
Got any more tax?
I know, I know, I know.
Yes, it was a good idea to come.
How does Jeff get ideas like that?
Hey, what's this, this, this, this?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Maybe this list of coming activities is where Jeff gets ideas
It was a good deal coming here tonight double dating with Jeff and Phyllis and me and your cake
Or you can ask K to go on dates with you alone if K would like it or you may plan for a weenie stroking
another group
A chance to learn the give and take of playing together.
On all fours, doing things in a bout,
wonder if she'd like to go to a baseball game.
A date that's not too, too, too.
Got something.
Here, watch this.
Do you want a date, I think? Let me see.
Look at this one.
It's from a movie of the violent years.
The other boss, chief.
You
That's so many questions. You might find the answer.
Jerry, be careful.
That's a beautiful sweater. Take it off.
What are you talking about?
You ain't got stuff in your ears. Take that sweater off.
But what right do you have?
Shut up and do as she says.
Do what they say, Shirley. They've got guns.
Yes, Shirley. We've got guns.
You're very observant for a pretty boy.
For God's sake, Cheryl, take this sweater off.
Give it to her.
Now, Buster, put your turn.
Step out.
Turn around.
Put your hands out in front of you.
Being Ford, put your hands on the car door.
Come on, come on, we haven't got all night.
You've seen this done before.
How lousy 11 bucks your characters ought to learn to carry more dough. You can stand up now
Maybe he's got more to offer than his money. What are you getting at?
big
Strong little pretty maybe but yeah under conventional circumstances. He could be very interesting
Why wait for conventional circumstance? You got a point there. What about her? Oh tire up and toss in the back of the seat
Tire up you heard
You'd like to tell me what I used to tire up with user skirt that looks strong enough care up use it
You heard her girl get a move on
Now back to you, Hanson.
Look, you have my money.
You have my watch. You have my ring.
What more do you want?
Toss in the back of the seat.
Okay, but you mind telling me where we're going?
Some place where it's safe.
Just follow us.
Hey, yeah, this is the first thing.
Hey, it's Saiki.
Excuse me, one second.
It's me, how long?
It's alright.
Yeah, hey, sorry.
Hello.
Yeah, hey.
Good, good, good.
We didn't do the fours.
The forest gump! This is forest gump!
I'm kidding, what's up, man? What's up?
Wait a second, it's almost over. It's 8 o'clock.
Hold it.
I want to have Christine, please.
Hey, what do you want?
Well, how are you doing?
I'm doing better than you.
What do you want?
OK.
Well, you sound like you have a terrible throat
condition now.
You enjoy making fun of my throat.
You know, we're going to make America great again.
We're going to do it.
Oh, you sound like Donald Trump, Christine.
Are you turning into Donald Trump or something?
I know.
Listen here, psych.
I and Sweet Pea have been talking.
Is this the only strong person to be Christine?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
This is Christine.
I and Sweet Pea have been talking.
You haven't?
And we're both gonna take a break.
You guys have been taking breaks for months.
I mean, you keep coming back instantly.
I mean, the next day I turn on, you're having an eight-hour show.
What's going on? You keep saying you're gonna take a break.
I mean, I said that sometimes, too.
I'll take a day. Two times, too.
I need a break, especially from you.
I'm tired of you.
I'm not even allowed on your show.
Good. You shouldn't be platforms on YouTube.
I mean, I can't even do my own show.
No, you shouldn't be able to do anything.
Okay, we're tired of you. You're tired of me? Well, you don't have to watch your green eyes.
If anyone wants to watch you. I do watch. I watch so I could flag it. Oh
Yeah, that's not nice. Why do you do that? I flag it for boring or boring as content. That's what I flag it for
boring? Well, let's say you can just like, you know, not watch it, watch something else.
You know, sometimes that or something, I think a lot of people watch the show to go to sleep
too, because they just get bored by it, so they fall asleep to it.
Some type of ASMR, you think? Yeah, your voice gives them a night orgasm.
You think my voice is actually night psyche?
Um, yeah, please. Beautiful. Oh.
How do you know all of a sudden I've had a change of heart?
I think you have a great show, actually.
I'm sorry.
Well, Christine.
You're actually a great guy.
The little halo above your head.
Well, you know, I'm not good or bad.
I'm like a balance.
Are you stretching?
Yeah, I'm stretching my legs.
Oh!
Did you see the thing that is his legs earlier?
Oh, I thought, I'm so sorry.
I saw, yeah, he has legs.
Remember when we made a bet, does he have no legs?
Or is in a wheelchair?
Or he has legs and he's just not standing up to be stubborn?
Or he, um, he's a good guy.
You guys keep making fun of him.
I don't understand this.
I know, but we haven't figured out what's
wrong with his legs yet, because there is something wrong.
He still doesn't really walk around.
We haven't seen him walk around.
He's always in his chair.
I don't think they're real legs.
I saw the legs, but I don't know if they're real.
I didn't see them move.
He has the greatest legs in America.
Did you make Donald Trump and you did AI on a thing that is
in exchange for, like, some kind of...
What's going on here? There must be a mind-blowing...
I don't know.
I think things legs are...
The thing that is might be AI himself,
but I think at least his legs are for sure.
Well, he doesn't have any hair on his legs.
You saw that?
Well, he's... I mean, maybe he's a woman.
Do you think that's why he considers himself a thing? That's why his name is thing
Yeah, it should be like man that is or woman that is choose one or the man that was that is a woman now
The man that was
Exchange thing have you are you a woman that became a man or a man like being a woman thing?
Possibly you never know now are things I mean are they using me here didn't worry me all that what's going on
Are you have anything interesting to say?
He said he's not hairy, I mean, we could tell.
I don't care what you mean.
The first day we saw you.
Yeah, he's not hairy.
I was just touching his legs, leaving me alone.
I mean, respectfully, we saw, we noticed that he's not hairy.
I mean, the bald head gave it away.
Come on.
How about, let's talk about what a two-faced you are.
What do you mean?
How you're like, you know, you're like, hey, we're a friend, and then you're like in
other places, like talking shit about me.
Oh, my God. Okay. What did I say on other places? Please tell me scumbag. I mean, you know, you should never donate to me.
What?
So I was a bad person. You said, you know, you're never going to talk to me again. You hate me. You said, um,
No, me. Oh, come on.
Didn't she say those things about me?
I did, but a couple of weeks ago when you had me blocked all over the place.
You're my mod. You're saying that.
But you you banned me for no reason the other day I read my look at all the things you said
I mean eventually I had I said it because you said it and you did it
Okay, it's fine, but okay, I'll take that. I mean Arthur's fine, but
Thank you
Why was in the moment it was in the moment just like you get pissed off in the moment
I got
Arthur you have some kind of the impulse control right now
Like why why do you come in calm like what it's like the same arm?
McQueen does the same thing. He's like he starts going off on me for no reason. Don't compare me to him. Yeah, you're like him
Sorry, I mean you are
You're both gay
Hello
You leave he left over that
Arthur. He didn't leave.
No, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Oh, yeah.
He's got the shit out of me.
Sorry about that, brother.
You're a good dude. It's like, you're a good dude.
Well, maybe not. Maybe I'm a bad person. I've just been like...
I mean, look, don't get me wrong, though.
I love to say, oh, he's a fucking scumbag to everybody when I'm not on panel.
Why do you say that to everybody?
I say that to everyone though.
But why?
That's just me pushing buttons.
I don't mean it.
You think people, all right, hold on.
You think people really believe me when I say that about everyone?
Come on.
Yeah.
No.
Your credibility makes me believe you.
At the end of the day, everyone here is an adult.
They make their own choices. I I can't as much as I want to tell someone something
At the end of the day, they have their own mind and they have their own
Tell me something good
Yeah, thanks for entering
I want to hear something good
You want to hear these?
Bullshit, so is there some good news or is there any kind you have to say or is there like, you know
Just want to talk to the same instigating bullshit
I see you're, you're the one that's antagonizing me.
I'm antagonizing you.
Yeah, you're like, what do you want?
Like, what, like, say, get the shit out.
If I come into your, your chat, if you had a chat,
and then I, and I'm bothering you,
like, you're like, you're bothering me right now.
Like, what would you do?
I'd be like, psyche, you know what?
You're going to have to come up on panel
and we're going to have to talk.
Oh, so you, you, we want more of me.
She's, and you want to, you want to put me on a panel
actually for that.
I would just want to clarify what's going on.
Yeah, but do I really want to like have a conversation for hours and hours and hours back and forth with you, Arthur?
In different sweeties voice, Christine's voice. I mean, I'd say I don't know.
I know that's how you felt about me.
Do you want to know that we can make up?
What the fuck?
Do you know what the best part of fighting is? It's the make-up sex.
Come on baby, you know, I don't he's either you or Q coming to move in with me. I'd rather have you know, like you probably
Anyways, um, what's going on to the chat K in the chat if I'm not gonna have a wrench
I think K deserves a wrench. Okay, I'll give a K the one I was gonna give to you
She's uh, she's a good girl. Are you K is K one of your sock puppet accounts?
She's a good person man.
Okay, okay.
Take care.
Is her name KKK?
Uh, dude, come on dude, she's, don't do that.
We just watched something and they made that joke, it was kind of dumb, I'm sorry.
Don't do that, don't ever insult or like that again.
Anyways, what are your thoughts on seafood?
Do you like boil, what is it, broiled crabs or what is it?
Padlegs, you like stuff like that?
I like oysters, Rockefeller.
I like different kinds of fish.
I like calamari.
I like all kinds of fish.
I love fish.
I love, I love fish sticks in your mouth.
Fish sticks.
Ha ha ha.
Get it?
You know, yeah, I get it.
Uh, I'm a big fan of, um, the bradblades, bro.
I'm a big fan of your legs.
Oh my god.
What?
Why do you always freak out about everything?
I feel like you actually interact with me serious when I do an impersonation.
Yeah
I feel like I'm talking to Josh like a bore or something. I mean, it's I don't know
You're very racist. It's because I'm brown. I'm brown. Is that's why?
No, you're less and plus you're lighter than I am so you're not brown. No, no you fuck
I am I am brown as it gets
Okay, this is the only way I'm gonna ever get to talk to you in a normal way is with art
It's Arthur being it. I mean, it's like otherwise. It's like I always it's always a screaming fight with you
You and I we are like water and oil
Well, what am I the oil or the water? You're the water and I'm the oil cuz I'm Arab
Okay, oh, you understand that. Yeah, that's a good one Arthur. It's good. Yes
You're you're clear like the water and I am a sleazy hack like the oil very greasy
well I mean that's a little bit I am Arab you understand I am the oil you are
but no you're you're not Arab you said you're like Persian I'm Arab Persian
Indian whatever you want I'm brown and I wear the turban all the same thing all
the same turban has like a little lull in the tongue
turban? turban oh you're making fun of my accent now?
yeah I am
You are very disgusting. Fuck you
Anyway psyche, I'm calling to tell you um, I've spoken to my two other ladies. I do will be taking a break
I do will be taking a break. I don't know if you heard
Okay, I'll let me take a break too
That is perfectly understandable. You you just tired me out so quick. I can't
Can't what I
Just can't keep up with you like one day of your stream. It's like a whole year here in the community
Know I have that's why I have it up. I'm not material till I like last a lifetime
I can retire now, and this is why you get no donations
What did you say ah
I get no donations. I did not say that. What did you saying? I love you psyche
You're going to love bomb you I do the bomb, but I do the love bomb
Well, it sounds nice
Oh, this is the love bomb. I love bomb you. Okay
What's better than bombing with the actual bomb? No, I know do that. There's someone, you know
No comment. Um, I
Love bomb. I don't bomb. I love bomb
Understand
Anyways, I'm waiting for you're waiting for your love bomb for over a year and so
Well, maybe if you stop being so fake, you're a very fake very fake
I'm okay. I'm fake. Okay. The other day. I went to Chinatown. I went to go buy some purging jewelry and guess what?
What the jewelry is not as fake as you fuck you
You make my neck turn green
Was that like the jewelry you made yes, yes
Well, I'm gonna say I'm gonna say I don't want to be me. I don't I don't I don't want to cause wrong
It's something stop doing that or there are even your new character. Can you have on a part? All right?
What do you want me to do? I want a punchy's voice
You can do um, uh Yvana has like a southern accent like hey, they are psyche over here. This is a little Yvana
Okay, now I want to punch you
Q45s voice I can't really have an actually a psyche what I suck my dick
He doesn't really have an accent
Yvana does that we've
Hey, this is their Yvonne.
I got my boots on.
Is it Yvonne or Bunchy Trump?
That's her mental name.
Her mental name is Bunchy.
Actually, it's Trump Daughter.
Hey, my name is Yvonne.
Mostly, this is Yvonne here.
And I deserve to have a wrench in the chat.
And I expect nothing less.
It's like, yeah, I've got your back here.
So it's day one.
She had something like that, but they're like, they're kapaw.
Oh yeah, I've got a little straw in my mouth.
Is she in the chat right now?
Or should she like, you know, get in the chat?
No, she's not in the chat right now.
This is all right now on StreamYard.
What's, what comprehension don't you want to say?
I know there's no reason to chat.
When we're very anxious, she's watching.
All right, so who, who do you want me to do then?
Like, shit, you want me to do Sandman's?
Let's do Sandman.
Yeah, just say man.
All right.
Ahem.
Parking.
It's all right.
All right, what's up?
Hey, lovebug, I'm stupid.
How are you?
Did you just call me a lovebug?
No, I'm not stupid.
I know you're stupid.
No, you're stupid.
I'm not stupid.
You're stupid.
I'm an idiot.
No, you're dumb.
Hey, do you have your hook out?
I've got my hook. Yes. Very hook. Wait, hold on. Why don't I turn it to Beeta?
It was Beeta's voice again.
It was not even Beeta. It sounded like, it's like Ayatollah Khomeini's voice or something.
Very obscure. I don't even know. It's very obscure.
Alright, so who the fuck? Who else? Who else doesn't like you?
You can do Amanda.
I'm I don't recall how she sounds she sounds like a care. I don't recall to be honest
Okay, whatever. How about can you do?
DJ lecture hey there psyche no, I can't
That was your like, Christine voice plus the beautiful voice.
I don't even know what that was.
I don't know.
I want to tickle your other voice.
I tickle you, Arthur.
What?
I tickle you?
No.
What?
I tickle your funny bone.
No.
I mean, that means make you laugh.
I'm good.
Can I um okay, do you want to have a contest and whoever can like wear a diaper and not pee for the longest wins?
What is that a thing?
It can be a breeze we started
What the fuck do you want to do that we might get famous doing that?
And we get that we can hose ourselves off and then wrestle naked
Weird diapers and let's see who can hold on to the list the longest with only fans for a million dollars
What the fuck?
Because we're straight guys like making out. So you you you're into some weird shit, huh?
Yeah, I like you I
Weird you're not weird and stop. Yeah, I'm not gay dude. I know you're not gay
But let me see what would you do you would like? Hey, you would have a threesome with another guy. No, who said I would
I'm just thinking, I think you can't laugh.
You would like, you would like do double penetration
with another guy and like rub your wieners together
and one of them is vagina.
I know you would do that if you were drunk enough.
And you would kiss a guy if you were drunk.
You would like, you would like,
just try to pretend you're,
you started, some guy started to give you a blow job
and you were like, you know, kind of passed out.
You just let him finish.
And that-
Is this what you dream of?
Yeah.
Think about it a lot. I'm a whole diary. I'm a dedicated to it
What the hell? It's called my nightmares about Arthur
Until no, it's how Arthur's nightmares. I'm just kidding. I don't I didn't do that. Oh, so
Whatever happened to that Chinese girl yummy
Yeah, what a robber
Eat so I died. They thought I was yummy. I knew me
Whatever happened to her someone ate me for that. I was yummy, but I knew me
Is she still around?
Hello, I died. I had eaten
That was yummy, but I knew me come pouch chicken
Or shut up
Well, I've been her. She's a little weirdo, huh? I think I think the Palestinians got involved and it's all over
She was weird like she was like against like I forgot what like the religions and she was Muslim or something
She was um, she I think she was one of the out of the African
Go her wife
My fuck that bitch. Hey, excuse me. What?
What if she could be dead for all you know, we don't say that
She's not dead do she ever do to you
It's just never mind
Okay, I'm sorry to make it uncomfortable. I
Mean, I could do a great RG voice. Okay, I can't really like do it for too long. Okay. Let's hear. Hey, I want to hear your voice
Yeah, hey, thank you
Hi, it's Weepy.
Hey, no, I want to speak to Seiki.
Seiki's not here.
Yeah, well, I'm out of here then.
They don't go. I'm lonely.
Stop, stop. See?
Stop. We're not doing that. No, we're not doing that. Not chill.
I want to talk to Seiki. Come on, chill.
It's like he's dead. I killed him.
Stop.
I killed him. What's that?
No, no, see when I just
I told him to I told him to jump up a bridge and he did oh
When I do sweepies voice, I don't do I don't say stuff like that. Come on
No, this is the real sweepie
Right there stop stop
Right there we kiss what?
Yeah, can you see us?
Oh, Joe, what are you doing, bro?
Sweetie, what a dude.
Joe, come on, I want you to do the RG in personation, come on.
Hey, it's RG over here.
Hey, Arthur, I'm a raccoon in my picture.
What was this, a beautiful animal?
Hey, this is RG who's going on there.
Hey, I'm the real RG. This is not the real RG.
What is this? Who's this duffelhead?
What are you talking about?
No, you're not.
I'm the RG. I'm RG. I'm RG.
This is my DSM.
Radio live.
You're so pathetic.
Anyways, Colin here to talk about some...
That's your Christine voice.
No, this is Ergy. This is Ergy.
Oh my god.
Colin, to let you know, I will be filing the complaint
in a restraining order against you, site.
But what?
Uh, hold on, clumsy has been threatening me since I went on your panel last week.
He's acting like a complete psychopath.
This is why I hate that guy.
I was nice to him last week and he started to harass me.
Sexually harass you?
This is what, uh, Crystal Marie.
Oh.
Well, Crystal Marie probably taught him how to do it.
Uh, Crystal Marie, come on, come on panel.
And let's, uh, let's clear this up.
Clear the air.
I
Arthur do you know cat might one of my cats came back like a but not treks, but a different cat came back up for like a year
What's bro? Yeah, okay, so Crystal's here. What's it?
Come on panel crystal Marie, I think Chris somebody's backstage
There she is I only came up to say I spoke with the other three ladies and
And I'm gonna be taking a break
Yeah, the other three ladies
What
Arthur he's a sweepy Christine
You don't get it's like either you don't never mind never mind
God I was wanting
I fell for it.
You're not interested enough to try it.
You're talking speed.
Voluntary crystal will protect you my lady
There she is
Yeah, but my
Cat was like with their waiting or when I woke up that my black cat was like back on the leg and like the cabinet
Chris more remake pretend that she's interesting enough to threaten. Come on
Fucking wackado
Chris you know what Jack Parsons and Chris Marie are the fathers of rocketry as we know it today
Well, yeah, I mean, it's like I mean he he'd been to the rocket and then she did it again
We just think she said it was like a small projectile thing. I like a camp or something
So everything she just says is solid gold
Right completely believable. No, but then I just repeat what she said and then she's like, oh, you're making fun of me
I know I'm not I'm like
Seriously, that was what you said. You said you were
You're saying that her last name is not one brawn that's what you're saying
No, no, that's Eva broad like one brawn
Crystal being a, you know, ancestor of Hitler, I can't even talk about Hitler.
Wait, Hitler's not gay? Or was gay?
He's not gay.
Evil Lebron, you never heard of that?
No.
Hitler liked it, but he was into it.
I know about the rack pat.
Were you educated in America, fucking Arthur?
I was raised in Haiti.
It makes a lot more sense though.
Yes.
Haitians are barely people.
They barely count as people.
It's true.
There's a couple of Haitians.
I think they're better than African-Americans.
They're not.
They are not.
Come on.
You don't mean that.
I know one Haitian in the U.S. community.
He sucks, too.
Art, I wanted to ask you, how was your show?
It was fun. I tried to make it as funny as I could
What are there to go? I
Don't know, but I think we're
You want to go work at more impressions?
Wow. Oh well. I don't know what you're talking about, but did your opinion change? Was it
better or worse than you expected? Like how did you like, I was more laid back than I
expected. I would like her to go on my show completely wasted and drunk because I think
that's funny.
But I don't know she still has me locked in her chat Alex if you're listening please unblock me. That would be more fun
I think I earned at least that I
Think she's been she hasn't been on blocking some people. Oh shit. Yeah, but
Still blue she's nuts but then again, we're all a little cookie aren't we psych?
Right, I mean, I don't think I think that's what human beings are we're like we have these brains and we're these very psychological beings
And there's a million things going on psychological with all of us
We'd have spirit so that's we can have again, you know different different fractures and for different traumas and different
You know splits and stuff like that all I mean just like there's so much
There's been programmed all our lives since like since everything and sometimes for the various purposes
But we're out of our natural element a lot
So I beg for the Haitian that everyone leaves, I didn't know they were a super power.
Oh well.
Well, I mean, it's like, I don't really, I don't think I'm making fun of anybody.
I just like, you know, I think that we can make fun of people equally.
I don't think there's anybody that's off the limits.
I would like for Chris Morita to come up and explain to us how she is being targeted
And by who she's claiming it's clumsy this week. It was Sam and last week. It's always someone crystal
I want it. We want to see proof. Maybe she isn't lying
You know, maybe crystal Marie isn't just completely making this up. You need to come up with proof
I'd like to see I think other people would like to see as well
What I didn't think it was a big deal. I wasn't the only kid there
What the fuck is he babbling about?
He's talking about the rock.
She was at a camp.
You know those ones where they take a bottle of like, you know,
you can put baking soda in a fucking vinegar,
and she's trying to say, uh...
She did that, and she won that contest,
and she thinks I was expecting a book of Guinness Records
or something.
If you put baking soda, and I think it's vinegar in a bottle,
it's gonna have a reaction to some of it.
Yeah, I mean, that's standardly science.
This is gonna make you a grandmother of fucking modern rock and re...
Sometimes, like, they have, like, walk...
Maybe it was, like, they play with water guns or something.
I don't know what they're doing.
or what you got in her head that someone said,
oh, we're the Guinness Book of World Records.
That was one of the fastest one.
And she never went to the period.
I don't know if Crystal knows this, too,
but I invented volcanoes at the science fair.
I made a paper shape volcano and a little baking soda
to that motherfucker.
Yeah, and since then, I'm the guy who invented them.
And she didn't know that.
Put that feather in your cap, Crystal.
I'm going to look at the Guinness Book of World Records right now and verify your claims.
That was a big deal. I wasn't in the...
That's not the guy who invented volcanoes.
That means they're all dead.
There were witnesses that means right there's witnesses there and yeah, huh? There's a whole science
Fairful of witnesses who you kids it was a size of a bottle
We made it out of peppers machine paper mache and bottle rocket parts. Just talk about a fucking science fair
Crystal was called the science fair, you know,
that you were doing, like, different projects.
That was a serious business.
You were doing a science fair?
Dude, NASA was that Crystal Marie science fair.
I won first place in the science fair.
It was a middle school science fair.
Everyone else had all these crazy, like, projects
with volcanoes and stuff.
I just said, what paper towel is more absorbent,
like, bounty or brawny?
And I seriously won.
the
Like with grapes and then put over the swimming pool and like whatever really broke first
Yeah, the fucking Chinese kid always wins exactly thing that is the fuck a little cute kid
He didn't win, but I was a spelling bee and the black kid wasn't a spelling bee
What's a good thing the Chinese kid won because if he didn't win his mother would be into a pulp
What's all you mean you got a peep us
There is a guilt trip that I mean the kids are I mean the Chinese like are
No, mom. No, oh you could take on this a b-plus. Oh
I take it out of your ass. Oh come on. No mom. No
It's what come on. That's how the jet mothers are all right. They're all like
Huh, how dare you get anything less than a plus?
See Arthur, that's how you do voices
I'm trying to be like you you got it Arthur. Like I haven't been doing this for years. You just started doing it two weeks ago.
Fuck out of here. Seriously. I understand this weird show. See if you guys want to check this out.
You started doing this little girl voice too easy. Also. He's the king of impressions
I can do a little I can do it fucking seven or limit in person to
You're not some some talent fucking weirdo
I think I had too much coffee this morning
Nice by the English
Oh my god, you're trying to kill my family now Roblox, I'm really glad that you don't have the
I'm not going to where you live
Why
Hey thing hate to break it to you know what I'll leave it alone leave it alone
or fucking I'm not an illegal immigrant.
I'm not a criminal resident in New Zealand.
Let's go over there and let me know the panel on stuff there, right?
Well, why wouldn't you want to make the flight?
I want to make the United States.
You made a big deal about not wanting to make the flight.
Oh, the 150.
Oh look, Yumi's over there.
There's a fucking shot.
We found Yumi, folks.
She hasn't been stoned to death.
I'm about an hour and a half away from here.
Yumi's in chat.
Not stoned to death.
These people are fucking bored. Why are we watching this?
I don't know
Besides the fat chick and eat noodles and noodles
Living in America like your world is all good. Everything is great. They made a movie about it
I could get one person on this panel to commit suicide